<mets:mets xmlns:mets="http://www.loc.gov/METS/" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/METS/ https://www.loc.gov/standards/mets/mets.xsd" OBJID="oai:wwu.de:80536fca-9938-4066-95de-0c09ea3e82f6" LABEL="University of Muenster, Institutional Repository MIAMI"  xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
          <mets:metsHdr CREATEDATE="2022-04-07T09:40:56">
            <mets:agent TYPE="OTHER" ROLE="OTHER" OTHERTYPE="SOFTWARE">
              <mets:name>Memory Alpha</mets:name>
            </mets:agent>
          </mets:metsHdr>
          <mets:dmdSec ID="DMD_80536fca-9938-4066-95de-0c09ea3e82f6">
            <mets:mdWrap MIMETYPE="text/xml" MDTYPE="MODS">
              <mets:xmlData>
                <mods:mods xmlns:mods="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-7.xsd" version="3.7">
                  <mods:titleInfo type="uniform" lang="eng">
                    <mods:title>Including the Highly Gifted and Creative Students – Current Ideas and Future Directions</mods:title>
                    <mods:subTitle>Proceedings of the 11th International Conference on Mathematical Creativity and Giftedness (MCG 11) : 22.08.2019 – 24.08.2019 Universität Hamburg, Germany</mods:subTitle>
                  </mods:titleInfo>
                  <mods:name type="personal" valueURI="http://d-nb.info/gnd/122655028">
                    <mods:namePart type="given">Marianne</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:namePart type="family">Nolte</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:namePart type="date">1953-</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:displayForm>Nolte, Marianne</mods:displayForm>
                    <mods:role>
                      <mods:roleTerm type="code" authority="marcrelator">edt</mods:roleTerm>
                    </mods:role>
                  </mods:name>
                  <mods:name type="corporate" valueURI="http://d-nb.info/gnd/5091030-9" altRepGroup="2">
                    <mods:namePart>Universitäts- und Landesbibliothek Münster</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:role>
                      <mods:roleTerm type="code" authority="marcrelator">own</mods:roleTerm>
                    </mods:role>
                  </mods:name>
                  <mods:name type="corporate" valueURI="http://d-nb.info/gnd/5091030-9" altRepGroup="2">
                    <mods:namePart>Münster, Westfalen / ULB</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:role>
                      <mods:roleTerm type="code" authority="marcrelator">own</mods:roleTerm>
                    </mods:role>
                  </mods:name>
                  <mods:name type="corporate" valueURI="http://d-nb.info/gnd/5091030-9" altRepGroup="2">
                    <mods:namePart>Münster, Westfalen / Landesbibliothek</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:role>
                      <mods:roleTerm type="code" authority="marcrelator">own</mods:roleTerm>
                    </mods:role>
                  </mods:name>
                  <mods:name type="corporate" valueURI="http://d-nb.info/gnd/5091030-9" altRepGroup="2">
                    <mods:namePart>Westfalen / Universität Münster / Universitäts- und Landesbibliothek</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:role>
                      <mods:roleTerm type="code" authority="marcrelator">own</mods:roleTerm>
                    </mods:role>
                  </mods:name>
                  <mods:genre>conferenceObject</mods:genre>
                  <mods:genre authority="dct">Text</mods:genre>
                  <mods:originInfo>
                    <mods:publisher>WTM-Verlag für wissenschaftliche Texte und Medien</mods:publisher>
                    <mods:dateIssued keyDate="yes">2019</mods:dateIssued>
                    <mods:issuance>monographic</mods:issuance>
                  </mods:originInfo>
                  <mods:originInfo>
                    <mods:dateIssued encoding="w3cdtf">2019-12-12</mods:dateIssued>
                    <mods:dateModified encoding="w3cdtf">2019-12-12</mods:dateModified>
                    <mods:edition>[Electronic ed.]</mods:edition>
                  </mods:originInfo>
                  <mods:language>
                    <mods:languageTerm type="code" authority="iso639-2b">eng</mods:languageTerm>
                  </mods:language>
                  <mods:physicalDescription>
                    <mods:form>electronic</mods:form>
                    <mods:reformattingQuality>access</mods:reformattingQuality>
                    <mods:internetMediaType>application/pdf</mods:internetMediaType>
                    <mods:extent>384</mods:extent>
                    <mods:digitalOrigin>born digital</mods:digitalOrigin>
                  </mods:physicalDescription>
                  <mods:abstract lang="eng">This volume contains the papers presented at the 11th international Conference on Mathematical Crea­tivity and Giftedness (MCG 11) "Including the Highly Gifted and Creative Students – Current Ideas and Future Directions", held from 22.08.2019 – 24.08.2019 in Ham­burg.</mods:abstract>
                  <mods:tableOfContents lang="eng">CONTENT ..... 1&#13;
INTRODUCTION ..... 6&#13;
MAIN LECTURES ..... 7&#13;
RESEARCH ON MATHEMATICAL GIFTEDNESS IN GERMANY – LOOKING BACK AND AHEAD - TORSTEN FRITZLAR AND MARIANNE NOLTE ..... 8&#13;
TEACHING HIGHLY ABLE LEARNERS IN DIVERSE CLASSROOMS: PEDAGOGICAL POSSIBILITIES THROUGH COLLABORATION - ELISABET MELLROTH AND VALERIE MARGRAIN ..... 21&#13;
UNCERTAINTY AS A CATALYST FOR MATHEMATICAL CREATIVITY - BHARATH SRIRAMAN ..... 32&#13;
THEORETICAL CONSIDERATIONS  ..... 52&#13;
OVEREXCITABILITY, ICONOCLASM AND MATHEMATICAL CREATIVITY &amp; GIFTEDNESS - MATTHIAS BRANDL AND ATTILA SZABO ..... 53&#13;
THE INTERSECTION OF PROBLEM POSING AND CREATIVITY: A REVIEW - JULIA JOKLITSCHKE, LUKAS BAUMANNS, BENJAMIN ROTT  ..... 59&#13;
PROVIDING FOR GIFTED LEARNERS IN THE REGULAR MATHEMATICS CLASSROOM: NEEDS AND THE WAY FORWARD - JACK MATHOGA MARUMO ..... 68&#13;
SETTING THE CEILING TOO LOW FOR MATHEMATICALLY GIFTED STUDENTS IN SOUTH AFRICAN SCHOOLS - MICHAEL KAINOSE MHLOLO ..... 73&#13;
WHAT IS EPISTEMOLOGY OF THE IMAGINATION? THEORY- EPISTEMOLOGICAL BASES TO MATHEMATICAL REASONING - LUIS MAURICIO RODRÍGUEZ-SALAZAR AND GUILLERMO S. TOVAR SÁNCHEZ ..... 79&#13;
RESEARCH ..... 86&#13;
GIRLS' PERFORMANCE IN THE KANGAROO CONTEST - MARK APPLEBAUM AND ROZA LEIKIN ..... 87&#13;
WHAT DO STUDENT TEACHERS BELIEF ABOUT MATHEMATICAL GIFTEDNESS? FIRST INSIGHTS OF AN EXPLORATORY STUDY - DANIELA ASSMUS AND RALF BENÖLKEN ..... 95&#13;
DISCERNING TWO CREATIVE ACTS: EXPANDING POSSIBILITIES AND DIVERGENT THINKING - AYMAN ALJARRAH AND JO TOWERS ..... 103&#13;
'LEMAS' – A JOINT INITIATIVE OF GERMANY'S FEDERAL GOVERNMENT AND GERMANY'S FEDERAL STATES TO FOSTER HIGH-ACHIEVING AND POTENTIALLY GIFTED PUPILS - RALF BENÖLKEN, FRIEDHELM KÄPNICK, WIEBKE AUHAGEN, LEA SCHREIBER ..... 109&#13;
SOCIO-MATHEMATICAL NORMS RELATED TO PROBLEM POSING IN A GIFTED CLASSROOM  - ASLI ÇAKIR AND HATICE AKKOÇ ..... 117&#13;
COLLECTIVE CREATIVITY IN MATHEMATICS: POSSIBLE SCENARIOS FOR SHARED MATHEMATICAL CREATIVITY - ALEXANDRE T. DE CARVALHO, CLEYTON H. GONTIJO, MATEUS G. FONSECA ..... 124&#13;
AN INITIAL INVESTIGATION INTO TEACHER ACTIONS THAT SPECIFICALLY FOSTER MATHEMATICAL CREATIVITY - EMILY CILLI-TURNER, MILOS SAVIC, HOUSSEIN EL TURKEY, GULDEN KARAKOK ..... 130&#13;
COMPARISON OF GIFTED AND MAINSTREAM 9TH GRADE STUDENTS’ STATISTICAL REASONING TYPES - TUGAY DURAK AND FATMA ASLAN TUTAK ..... 136&#13;
IMPROVING MATHEMATICAL MOTIVATION FROM MATHEMATICAL CREATIVITY WORKSHOPS - MATEUS G. FONSECA, CLEYTON H. GONTIJO, MATHEUS D. T. ZANETTI, ALEXANDRE T. DE CARVALHO ..... 144&#13;
FOSTERING YOUNG CHILDREN’S CREATIVE MINDS: KINDERGARTEN KIDS EXPLORE SCHOOL-BASED STEM LAB - VIKTOR FREIMAN AND XAVIER ROBICHAUD ..... 150&#13;
CREATIVE AND CRITICAL THINKING IN MATHEMATICS: A WORKSHOP FOR TEACHERS - CLEYTON HÉRCULES GONTIJO, MATHEUS DELAINE TEIXEIRA ZANETTI, MATEUS GIANNI FONSECA ..... 158&#13;
“BUT PAINTING IS MORE FUN” ON INTERVENTION POSSIBILITIES FOR UNDERACHIEVERS IN MATHEMATICS EDUCATION - HEIKE HAGELGANS ..... 163&#13;
“OH, I DO NOT LIKE THAT WHEN YOU HAVE TO JUSTIFY SOMETHING” – DIFFICULTIES IN FORMULATING ARGUMENTS AS A BASIS FOR THE SUPPORT OF MATHEMATICAL GIFTEDNESS - SIMONE JABLONSKI AND MATTHIAS LUDWIG ..... 171&#13;
EXPLORATION OF UNKONWN: A DIFFERENT APPROACH TO FOSTER MATHEMATICAL CREATIVITY - VINAY NAIR AND HARI RAMASUBRAMANIAN ..... 178&#13;
SELECTION CRITERIA FOR STUDENTS IN A DANISH MATHEMATICS TALENT PROGRAM - LÓA BJÖRK JÓELSDÓTTIR AND DORTHE ERREBO-HANSEN ..... 185&#13;
MATHEMATICALLY GIFTED STUDENTS’ REFLECTIONS ON USING HISTORY OF MATHEMATICS IN MATHEMATICS CLASSROOM - FIRDEVS ICLAL KARATAS AND MINE ISIKSAL BOSTAN ..... 191&#13;
STUDENTS’ CONCEPTIONS OF MATHEMATICAL CREATIVE THINKING AND CRITICAL THINKING IN STEM PBL ACTIVITIES - YUJIN LEE, ROBERT M. CAPRARO, MARY M. CAPRARO, KATHERINE VELA, DANIELLE BEVAN, CASSIDY CALDWELL ..... 197&#13;
TASKS THAT ENHANCE CREATIVE REASONING: SUPPORTING GIFTED PUPILS IN INCLUSIVE EDUCATION SYSTEMS - ANITA M. SIMENSEN AND MIRJAM H. OLSEN ..... 202&#13;
EXAMINING PRIMARY SCHOOL TEACHER-SUPPORT TOWARDS MATHEMATICALLY GIFTED LEARNERS IN SOUTH AFRICA - MOTSHIDISI GERTRUDE VAN WYK AND MICHAEL KAINOSE MHLOLO ..... 209&#13;
STEM PROJECT-BASED LEARNING ACTIVITIES: OPPORTUNITIES TO ENGAGE IN CREATIVE MATHEMATICAL THINKING? - KATHERINE VELA, DANIELLE BEVAN, CASSIDY CALDWELL, ROBERT M. CAPRARO, MARY MARGARET CAPRARO, YUJIN LEE ..... 215&#13;
ANALOGICAL TRANSFER AND COGNITIVE FRAMING IN PROSPECTIVE TEACHERS’ PROBLEM POSING ACTIVITIES - CRISTIAN VOICA AND FLORENCE MIHAELA SINGER ..... 222&#13;
PROBLEM SOLVING IN SECONDARY EDUCATION: A QUALITATIVE ANALYSIS OF THE DIFFERENCES BETWEEN HIGHLY AND MILDLY GIFTED STUDENTS - ELINE WESTERHOUT, ISABELLE VAN DRIESSEL, BJÖRN VAN DER HELM ..... 229&#13;
PROSPECTIVE TEACHERS’ VIEWS ON MATHEMATICAL GIFTEDNESS AND ON TEACHERS OF MATHEMATICALLY GIFTED STUDENTS - GÖNÜL YAZGAN-SAĞ ..... 236&#13;
IMPROVING MATHEMATICAL CREATIVITY IN THE CLASSROOM: A CASE STUDY OF A FOURTH-GRADE TEACHER - ARIANTHI ZIOGA AND DESPINA DESLI ..... 242&#13;
PROPOSALS FOR PRACTICE  ..... 249&#13;
MAGIC POLYGONS AND ITS USAGE IN WORK WITH GIFTED PUPILS - ELĪNA BULINA AND ANDREJS CIBULIS ..... 250&#13;
GROUP THEORY VIA SYMMETRIES FOR ENRICHMENT CLASSES FOR GIFTED YOUTH - KARL HEUER AND DENIZ SARIKAYA ..... 257&#13;
EXTENSION AND DEVELOPMENT OF DIFFERENT NON-NEWTONIAN CALCULUS IN ORDER TO SOLVE DIFFERENT DIFFERENTIAL AND DIFFERENCE EQUATIONS BASED ON MATHEMATICAL EDUCATION APPROACHES - M. JAHANSHAHI AND N. ALIEV ..... 264&#13;
PÓSA METHOD: TALENT NURTURING IN WEEKEND MATH CAMPS - PÉTER JUHÁSZ AND DÁNIEL KATONA ..... 270&#13;
MATHEMATICS EDUCATION PRE-SERVICE TEACHERS AWARENESS OF GIFTED STUDENTS’ CHARACTERISTICS - LUKANDA KALOBO AND MICHAEL KAINOSE MHLOLO ..... 277&#13;
SIMPLE BUT USEFUL TASKS WITH GEOMETRICAL CONTENT AND CREATIVE FLAVOUR - ROMUALDAS KAŠUBA AND EDMUNDAS MAZĖTIS ..... 284&#13;
VISUALIZATION OF THE FIRST STEPS OF NUMBER THEORY FOR ELEMENTARY SCHOOL CHILDREN – A PYTHAGOREAN APPROACH - PETER KOEHLER ..... 290&#13;
INCUBATING MATHEMATICAL CREATIVITY THROUGH A MOLECULAR GASTRONOMY 101 SATURDAY ENRICHMENT CAMP - CONNY PHELPS ..... 296&#13;
IT’S NOT ALWYS SIMPLER TO USE “MAKE IT SIMPLER” - WILLIAM R. SPEER ..... 304&#13;
PEDAGOGY OF IMAGINATION: EPISTOMOLOGICAL FOUNDATIONS TO DEVELOP MATHEMATICAL THINKING IN PRESCHOOL STUDENTS - LUIS MAURICIO RODRÍGUEZ-SALAZAR, CARMEN PATRICIA ROSAS-COLÍN, RAMSÉS DANIEL MARTÍNEZ-GARCÍA ..... 311&#13;
TASKS ON VISUAL PATTERNS AS THE FIRST STAGE OF INTRODUCING ALGEBRA CONCEPTS - INGRIDA VEILANDE ..... 319&#13;
CREATIVITY, TECHNOLOGY AND “OUT SCHOOL” INTERESTING MATHEMATICS WITH TECHNOLOGY DURING OUT SCHOOL - SHIN WATANABE ..... 327&#13;
WORKSHOP ..... 335&#13;
MATHEMATIZING CREATIVE STEM PBL ACTIVITIES - MARY M. CAPRARO, ROBERT M. CAPRARO KATHERINE N. VELA, CASSIDY CALDWELL, DANIELLE BEVAN, YUJIN LEE ..... 336&#13;
WORKSHOP: VARIATIONS IN OPEN PROBLEM FIELDS AS A TOOL FOR MATHEMATICAL EDUCATION: FROM BASICS TO OPEN QUESTIONS IN 90 MINUTES - KARL HEUER AND DENIZ SARIKAYA ..... 340&#13;
AN INTRODUCTORY WORKSHOP TO THE VISUALIZATION OF THE FIRST STEPS OF NUMBER THEORY FOR ELEMENTARY SCHOOL CHILDREN – A PYTHAGOREAN APPROACH - PETER KOEHLER ..... 342&#13;
SHAPE UP: PROVEN SPATIAL ACTIVITIES FOR ELEMENTARY STUDENTS - LINDA JENSEN SHEFFIELD ..... 345&#13;
SPIROGRAPH – A TOY AS A MATHEMATICAL PROBLEM - PETER STENDER ..... 347&#13;
SYMPOSIUM ..... 355&#13;
TAPPING MATHEMATICAL CREATIVITY THROUGH PROBLEM SOLVING: PROBLEM-MATRIX FRAMEWORK FOR TEACHING FOR CREATIVITY IN THE MATH CLASSROOM - A. KADIR BAHAR AND SINAN KANBIR ..... 356&#13;
RESEARCH WITHIN THE FRAMEWORK OF THE HAMBURGER MODEL FOR THE PROMOTION OF PARTICULARLY MATHEMATICALLY GIFTED CHILDREN AND ADOLESCENTS - NINA KRÜGER, MIEKE JOHANNSEN, LUCA F. SMOYDZIN, HENRIK GENZEL, MARGUERITE I. PERITZ, JAKOB MEYER, SÖREN FIEDLER, MONIKA DASEKING ..... 358&#13;
POSTER ..... 366&#13;
AFFECTS OF MATHEMATICALLY GIFTED STUDENTS RELATED TO REVOLVING DOOR MODELS - WIEBKE AUHAGEN ..... 367&#13;
CREATIVE PROCESSES OF FIRST GRADERS WORKING ON ARITHEMTIC OPEN TASKS - SVENJA BRUHN ..... 371&#13;
MATHEMATICAL INTERACTIONS WITH GIFTED ADOLESCENTS - RYAN D. FOX ..... 374&#13;
DIFFERENTIATED INSTRUCTION USING LEARNING MANAGEMENT SYSTEMS IN UPPER SECONDARY SCHOOL AND UNIVERSITY LEVEL – A RESEARCH PROPOSAL - ELISABET MELLROTH, MIRELA VINEREAN-BERNHOFF, MATTIAS BOSTRÖM, YVONNE LILJEKVIST ..... 378&#13;
RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT TASKS WITHIN THE FRAMEWORK OF THE PRIMA-PROJEKT IN HAMBURG ..... 381&#13;
MARIANNE NOLTE, KIRSTEN PAMPERIEN, KATRIN VORHÖLTER ..... 381</mods:tableOfContents>
                  <mods:targetAudience>specialized</mods:targetAudience>
                  <mods:note type="content">Druckausgabe: Nolte, Marianne (Hrsg.): Including the Highly Gifted and Creative Students – Current Ideas and Future Directions : Proceedings of the 11th International Conference on Mathematical Creativity and Giftedness (MCG 11) : 22.08.2019 – 24.08.2019 Universität Hamburg, Germany. Münster : WTM, 2019. (Conference Proceedings in Mathematics Education ; 5), ISBN 978-3-95987-131-0</mods:note>
                  <mods:note type="ownership">© 2019 WTM – Verlag für wissenschaftliche Texte und Medien, Münster</mods:note>
                  <mods:subject>
                    <mods:topic lang="ger">Mathematische Begabung; Mathematikunterricht</mods:topic>
                  </mods:subject>
                  <mods:classification authority="ddc">510</mods:classification>
                  <mods:classification authority="ddc">370</mods:classification>
                  <mods:relatedItem type="series">
                    <mods:titleInfo>
                      <mods:title script="Latn">Conference proceedings in mathematics education</mods:title>
                    </mods:titleInfo>
                    <mods:part type="volume" order="5">
                      <mods:detail>
                        <mods:number>5</mods:number>
                      </mods:detail>
                    </mods:part>
                    <mods:recordInfo>
                      <mods:recordIdentifier>oai:wwu.de:4cb868bf-7636-49d7-82fa-a70f54b19631</mods:recordIdentifier>
                    </mods:recordInfo>
                  </mods:relatedItem>
                  <mods:identifier type="urn">urn:nbn:de:hbz:6-82189522597</mods:identifier>
                  <mods:identifier type="isbn">978-3-95987-132-7</mods:identifier>
                  <mods:location>
                    <mods:url access="object in context">https://miami.uni-muenster.de/Record/80536fca-9938-4066-95de-0c09ea3e82f6</mods:url>
                  </mods:location>
                  <mods:accessCondition type="restriction on access">
                    <mods:extension>
                      <ma:maWrap xmlns:ma="http://memoryalpha.ulb.uni-muenster.de">
                        <ma:licence>
                          <ma:displayLabel>InC 1.0</ma:displayLabel>
                          <ma:targetUrl>https://rightsstatements.org/vocab/InC/1.0/</ma:targetUrl>
                        </ma:licence>
                      </ma:maWrap>
                    </mods:extension>
                  </mods:accessCondition>
                  <mods:recordInfo>
                    <mods:recordIdentifier>oai:wwu.de:80536fca-9938-4066-95de-0c09ea3e82f6</mods:recordIdentifier>
                  </mods:recordInfo>
                </mods:mods>
              </mets:xmlData>
            </mets:mdWrap>
          </mets:dmdSec>
          <mets:amdSec ID="AMD_80536fca-9938-4066-95de-0c09ea3e82f6">
            <mets:rightsMD ID="RIGHTSMD_80536fca-9938-4066-95de-0c09ea3e82f6">
              <mets:mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" MIMETYPE="text/xml" OTHERMDTYPE="DVRIGHTS">
                <mets:xmlData>
                  <dv:rights xmlns:dv="http://dfg-viewer.de/">
                    <dv:owner>Universitäts- und Landesbibliothek Münster</dv:owner>
                  </dv:rights>
                </mets:xmlData>
              </mets:mdWrap>
            </mets:rightsMD>
            <mets:digiprovMD ID="DIGIPROVMD_80536fca-9938-4066-95de-0c09ea3e82f6">
              <mets:mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" MIMETYPE="text/xml" OTHERMDTYPE="DVLINKS">
                <mets:xmlData>
                  <dv:links xmlns:dv="http://dfg-viewer.de/">
                    <dv:reference>https://miami.uni-muenster.de/Record/80536fca-9938-4066-95de-0c09ea3e82f6</dv:reference>
                    <dv:presentation/>
                  </dv:links>
                </mets:xmlData>
              </mets:mdWrap>
            </mets:digiprovMD>
          </mets:amdSec>
          <mets:fileSec>
            <mets:fileGrp USE="DEFAULT">
              <mets:file MIMETYPE="application/pdf" CHECKSUM="877e97a0fa0cce0be4b67e69f2803bb128c94be05cd68e0049fbb8bda20146a3" CREATED="2019-12-12T13:16:46" CHECKSUMTYPE="SHA-256" SIZE="11718642" ID="ID_FIL_wtm_isbn_978-3-95987-132-7.pdf_DEFAULT">
                <mets:FLocat xlink:href="https://repositorium.uni-muenster.de/document/miami/80536fca-9938-4066-95de-0c09ea3e82f6/wtm_isbn_978-3-95987-132-7.pdf" LOCTYPE="URL"/>
              </mets:file>
            </mets:fileGrp>
            <mets:fileGrp USE="DOWNLOAD">
              <mets:file MIMETYPE="application/pdf" ID="DOW80536fca-9938-4066-95de-0c09ea3e82f6">
                <mets:FLocat xlink:href="https://repositorium.uni-muenster.de/transfer/miami/80536fca-9938-4066-95de-0c09ea3e82f6" LOCTYPE="URL"/>
              </mets:file>
            </mets:fileGrp>
          </mets:fileSec>
          <mets:structMap TYPE="PHYSICAL">
            <mets:div ID="ID_PHY_80536fca-9938-4066-95de-0c09ea3e82f6" TYPE="physSequence">
              <mets:div ID="ID_PHY_wtm_isbn_978-3-95987-132-7.pdf">
                <mets:fptr FILEID="ID_FIL_wtm_isbn_978-3-95987-132-7.pdf_DEFAULT"/>
              </mets:div>
            </mets:div>
          </mets:structMap>
          <mets:structMap TYPE="LOGICAL">
            <mets:div ADMID="AMD_80536fca-9938-4066-95de-0c09ea3e82f6" DMDID="DMD_80536fca-9938-4066-95de-0c09ea3e82f6" ID="ID_LOG_80536fca-9938-4066-95de-0c09ea3e82f6" TYPE="Monograph">
              <mets:div ID="ID_LOG_ID_PHY_wtm_isbn_978-3-95987-132-7.pdf"/>
            </mets:div>
          </mets:structMap>
          <mets:structLink>
            <mets:smLink xlink:from="ID_LOG_80536fca-9938-4066-95de-0c09ea3e82f6" xlink:to="ID_PHY_80536fca-9938-4066-95de-0c09ea3e82f6"/>
            <mets:smLink xlink:from="ID_LOG_ID_PHY_wtm_isbn_978-3-95987-132-7.pdf" xlink:to="ID_PHY_wtm_isbn_978-3-95987-132-7.pdf"/>
          </mets:structLink>
        </mets:mets>