<mets:mets xmlns:mets="http://www.loc.gov/METS/" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/METS/ https://www.loc.gov/standards/mets/mets.xsd" OBJID="oai:wwu.de:a80ac83f-a3d6-4154-9345-5318eb9d15a6" LABEL="University of Muenster, Institutional Repository MIAMI"  xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
          <mets:metsHdr CREATEDATE="2022-04-07T17:51:36">
            <mets:agent TYPE="OTHER" ROLE="OTHER" OTHERTYPE="SOFTWARE">
              <mets:name>Memory Alpha</mets:name>
            </mets:agent>
          </mets:metsHdr>
          <mets:dmdSec ID="DMD_a80ac83f-a3d6-4154-9345-5318eb9d15a6">
            <mets:mdWrap MIMETYPE="text/xml" MDTYPE="MODS">
              <mets:xmlData>
                <mods:mods xmlns:mods="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-7.xsd" version="3.7">
                  <mods:titleInfo type="uniform" lang="ger">
                    <mods:title script="Latn">The Mathematics Education for the Future Project</mods:title>
                    <mods:subTitle>Proceedings of the 15th International Conference : Theory and Practice - an Interface or a Great Divide? 4-9 Aug, 2019, Maynooth University, Kildare, Ireland</mods:subTitle>
                  </mods:titleInfo>
                  <mods:name type="personal" valueURI="http://d-nb.info/gnd/107707713">
                    <mods:namePart type="given">Alan</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:namePart type="family">Rogerson</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:displayForm>Rogerson, Alan</mods:displayForm>
                    <mods:role>
                      <mods:roleTerm type="code" authority="marcrelator">edt</mods:roleTerm>
                    </mods:role>
                  </mods:name>
                  <mods:name type="personal">
                    <mods:namePart type="given">Janina</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:namePart type="family">Morska</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:displayForm>Morska, Janina</mods:displayForm>
                    <mods:role>
                      <mods:roleTerm type="code" authority="marcrelator">edt</mods:roleTerm>
                    </mods:role>
                  </mods:name>
                  <mods:name type="corporate" valueURI="http://d-nb.info/gnd/5091030-9" altRepGroup="3">
                    <mods:namePart>Universitäts- und Landesbibliothek Münster</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:role>
                      <mods:roleTerm type="code" authority="marcrelator">own</mods:roleTerm>
                    </mods:role>
                  </mods:name>
                  <mods:name type="corporate" valueURI="http://d-nb.info/gnd/5091030-9" altRepGroup="3">
                    <mods:namePart>Münster, Westfalen / ULB</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:role>
                      <mods:roleTerm type="code" authority="marcrelator">own</mods:roleTerm>
                    </mods:role>
                  </mods:name>
                  <mods:name type="corporate" valueURI="http://d-nb.info/gnd/5091030-9" altRepGroup="3">
                    <mods:namePart>Münster, Westfalen / Landesbibliothek</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:role>
                      <mods:roleTerm type="code" authority="marcrelator">own</mods:roleTerm>
                    </mods:role>
                  </mods:name>
                  <mods:name type="corporate" valueURI="http://d-nb.info/gnd/5091030-9" altRepGroup="3">
                    <mods:namePart>Westfalen / Universität Münster / Universitäts- und Landesbibliothek</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:role>
                      <mods:roleTerm type="code" authority="marcrelator">own</mods:roleTerm>
                    </mods:role>
                  </mods:name>
                  <mods:genre>conferenceObject</mods:genre>
                  <mods:genre authority="dct">Text</mods:genre>
                  <mods:originInfo>
                    <mods:publisher>WTM-Verlag für wissenschaftliche Texte und Medien</mods:publisher>
                    <mods:dateIssued keyDate="yes">2019</mods:dateIssued>
                    <mods:issuance>monographic</mods:issuance>
                  </mods:originInfo>
                  <mods:originInfo>
                    <mods:dateIssued encoding="w3cdtf">2019-08-08</mods:dateIssued>
                    <mods:dateModified encoding="w3cdtf">2022-04-07</mods:dateModified>
                    <mods:edition>[Electronic ed.]</mods:edition>
                  </mods:originInfo>
                  <mods:language>
                    <mods:languageTerm type="code" authority="iso639-2b">ger</mods:languageTerm>
                  </mods:language>
                  <mods:physicalDescription>
                    <mods:form>electronic</mods:form>
                    <mods:reformattingQuality>access</mods:reformattingQuality>
                    <mods:internetMediaType>application/pdf</mods:internetMediaType>
                    <mods:extent>xvi, 653</mods:extent>
                    <mods:digitalOrigin>born digital</mods:digitalOrigin>
                  </mods:physicalDescription>
                  <mods:abstract lang="eng">This volume contains the papers presented at the International Conference on Theory and Practice: An Interface or A Great Divide? and held from August 4-9, 2019 at Maynooth University, Kildare, Ireland. The Conference was organized by The Mathematics Education for the Future Project – an international educational project founded in 1986 and dedicated to innovation in mathematics, statistics, science and computer education world-wide.</mods:abstract>
                  <mods:tableOfContents lang="eng">Foreword by Alan Rogerson ..... v&#13;
Plenary Keynote Address by Douglas Butler: Can Technology make a Difference to Mathematics Education? ..... vi&#13;
Fouze Abu Oouder &amp; Miriam Amit: Incorporating Ethnomathematical Research in Classroom Practice - The Case of Geometrical Shapes in Bedouin Traditional Embroidery ..... 1&#13;
Nadine Adams &amp; Clinton Hayes: Providing Synchronous Mathematics Instruction to Distance Students - Workshop ..... 5&#13;
Kehinde Emmanuel Adenegan: Managing Pupils with Dysgraphia in Early Child Numeracy ..... 9&#13;
Cynthia O. Anhalt &amp; Ricardo Cortez: Mathematical Modeling Thinking: Laying the Foundation for Mathematical Modeling Competency ..... 14&#13;
Glenda Jean Ashleigh: Individual Differences in Cognition and Affect in Multiplicative Knowledge in Basic Mathematics Problems ..... 20&#13;
Katarzyna Banach: Ok Notebook as an Untypical Form of Student's Notebook - Own Experience ..... 26&#13;
Summer Bateiha &amp; Sadia Mir: Engaging with Mathematics through Three Types of Storytelling ..... 29&#13;
Mike Bedwell: Freedom of Speech ..... 34&#13;
Brianna Bentley: College Students’ Views of Fraction Arithmetic ..... 36&#13;
Paul Betts et al: Foundational Experiences as a Design Principle for Mathematics Curriculum for Children ..... 42&#13;
Esther Billings &amp; Lisa Kasmer: Learning via Teaching: Examples of Mediated Field Experiences in Early Coursework of Pre-service Teachers ..... 48&#13;
Daniel J. Brahier: Research into Practice: 29 Years of Classroom Teaching ..... 54&#13;
Sandra Browning: Elementary Preservice Teachers and Questioning Strategies in Mathematics ..... 60&#13;
Gail Burrill: Statistical Literacy and Quantitative Reasoning ..... 66&#13;
Cristina Cametti et al: Advantages, Challenges and Opportunities in Teaching Statistics in Doctoral Training to a Heterogeneous Group: the Case of FLAMES Summer School ..... 72&#13;
Luis Alexander Castro Miguez et al: Diagrammatic Reasoning from Reflections on Peircean Semiotics ..... 78&#13;
Olive Chapman &amp; Paulino Preciado Babb: Prospective Secondary Mathematics Teachers’ Development of Knowledge of Modelling for Teaching ..... 84&#13;
Kin Eng Chin &amp; Fui Fong Jiew: Misconceptions or Preconceptions in Making Sense of Decimals ..... 90&#13;
Marta Civil &amp; Roberta Hunter: Supporting Mathematics Teachers to Build Deep Understandings of the Home Contexts of their Students ..... 96&#13;
Katharine Clemmer et al: Collaborative Solution Discovery: A Problem Solving Process ..... 100&#13;
Porter Coggins et al: The Mathematical Culture of Ojibwe Students-An Ethnographic Study ..... 104&#13;
Ken Collins: Using CAS to Improve Student Understanding of Calculus Concepts ..... 110&#13;
Marjorie Curry: Culturally Responsive Math ..... 115&#13;
Bronislaw Czarnocha: Constructivist Teaching Experiment: Constructivist Research and Constructivist Teaching ..... 118&#13;
Mili Das: Curriculum for Mathematics Education – An Approach to Discuss Relation Between Theory and Practice ..... 124&#13;
Jan de Lange: Curious Minds: Serious Play ..... 130&#13;
Maifer Remzie Demirbec: Puerto Rico Gas Prices Fall – “The Math of Cheap Oil” ..... 136&#13;
Thomas P. Dick &amp; Mary E. Pilgrim: Learning (and Learning Teaching) by Doing Problems ..... 139&#13;
Pam Dorrington: Family Maths: Experiential Learning ..... 145&#13;
Daniela Ferrarello et al: Serious Games in Teaching/learning Mathematics: the Experience of FunGo ..... 150&#13;
Benjamin Fine et al: The Impact of Mathematics and Mathematicians ..... 156&#13;
Courtney Fox: Clean Water for Women and Children ..... 161&#13;
Ben Galluzzo &amp; Katie Kavanagh: Getting Started Getting Students Modeling: Designing and Facilitating Open-ended Math Modeling Experiences ..... 164&#13;
Avikam Gazit: Math Teachers' Attitudes toward Integrating Humor in Math Lessons ..... 168&#13;
Eoin Gill: Maths Week Ireland: Promoting a Positive Attitude to Mathematics in Ireland ..... 173&#13;
Joanne E. Goodell: Learning to Teach Mathematics Through Project-Based Instruction ..... 177&#13;
John Gordon et al: A Problem-Solving Approach to the Introduction to Ordinary Differential Equations for Undergraduate Students at an American Two-year College ..... 183&#13;
Ivona Grzegorczyk: Magic Tricks and Activities Supporting Abstract Thinking in Mathematics ..... 189&#13;
Irina Gurevich: Do Future Mathematics Teachers Need the Course "Integration of Digital Technologies in Teaching Mathematics", and if so, what exactly can it help them with? ..... 193&#13;
Heidi B. Hansen &amp; Marta T. Magiera: Working Together: A Cross-cultural Study Addressing Mathematics Anxiety in K-8 Pre-service Teachers ..... 199&#13;
Bradford Hansen-Smith: Why the Circle cannot be Squared ..... 205&#13;
Janet M.Herrelko: Change the Paradigm of Solitary Lesson Planning to Collaborative Planning that Unites Research and Practice ..... 211&#13;
Kenneth Horwitz: Utilizing Analytics to show Representations used in Comparing and Ordering Unit Fractions ..... 217&#13;
Hsin-Mei E. Huang et al: Investigating Junior High School Students’ Length Estimation Ability and Strategies ..... 223&#13;
Yuitza T. Humarán Martínez: Using Manipulatives to Develop the Understanding of the Concept of the Fraction of Preservice Elementary Teachers: The Meaning of Measure ..... 229&#13;
Debra L. Hydorn: Tools for Modern Mathematics: A Course to Introduce Experimental Mathematics ..... 235&#13;
Clement O. Iji &amp; Joseph A. Andortan: Brandishing Ethno-Mathematics Approach as an Interface for Improving Upper Basic Education (UBE) Students’ Interest and Achievement in Number and Numeration ..... 240&#13;
Hanan Innabi et al: Patterns of Variation in the Work of “Mathematics in the City Project”: A Suggested Research Question ..... 245&#13;
Colin Jackson: Going Against the Grain: Critical Thinking in and Beyond Mathematics ..... 251&#13;
Fui Fong Jiew &amp; Kin Eng Chin: The Embodiment of Mathematical Meanings with Special Reference to Multiplication: Issues and Challenges ..... 257&#13;
Peter Johnston et al: Supporting Transition for Mathematics and Science Students under an Assumed Knowledge Approach ..... 263&#13;
Sue Johnston-Wilder &amp; Clare Lee: How can we Address Mathematics Anxiety more Effectively as a Community? ..... 269&#13;
Luckson Muganyizi Kaino: Enhancing Mathematical Modeling Activities in Classroom Instruction ..... 275&#13;
Sylwia Kania: Solving Mathematical Problems in the Context of Some Obstacles between Teachers and Students ..... 281&#13;
Tierney Kennedy: Exploring the Nature of Teacher Questioning within Challenging Tasks for Inducing Conceptual Change ..... 287&#13;
Sergiy Klymchuk &amp; David Wilson: Integrating Pen-enabled Tablet PCs in Teaching Engineering Mathematics ..... 293&#13;
Steve Krevisky: Using Sports Data in Statistics and Math Classes: An Overview and Update ..... 299&#13;
Satoshi Kusaka: Analysis of the Characteristics of Mozambican Primary Mathematics Textbooks compared with Japanese Textbooks focusing on Tasks and Problems related to the Real World ..... 301&#13;
Katie Laskasky et al: Innovative Problem Solving: What happens when Math Education, Business, and Engineering Perspectives Interact ..... 306&#13;
Collette Lemieux &amp; Eric Roettger: Students’ Reasoning During a Calculus Two-Stage Exam ..... 312&#13;
Olga León Corredor et al: Integrating Technology and Didactic Resources for Enhancing Learning Processes. An Exploratory Study ..... 318&#13;
Su Liang: Enquiry-Based Learning in College Mathematics Education: Theory and Practice ..... 324&#13;
Alenka Lipovec &amp; Jasmina Ferme: Some Factors Influencing Effectiveness of Mathematics Homework ..... 330&#13;
Michael Lousis: Recommendations for Instructional Designers and Textbook Writers Concerning the Correction of Significant and Persistent Errors in Arithmetic and Algebra ..... 336&#13;
Patricia Marchand: Interface between Theoretical Guidelines and Classroom Practices to Create Activities that Enhance the Development of Spatial Reasoning in Elementary School ..... 343&#13;
Urška Markun &amp; Jasna Kos: Research Work in a Secondary School Classroom: How Well are Teachers Equipped for it? ..... 347&#13;
Malgorzata Mart: The Impact of Teacher Self-Efficacy on the Level of Implementation of Graphing Technology in Teaching Factoring Quadratic Functions in Introductory Algebra ..... 353&#13;
Ralph Mason et al: Foundational Experiences as a Curriculum Design Principle for Secondary Mathematics ..... 358&#13;
Bernie (Dov) May: Engage Students More Hopscotch Math has Students Jumping for Joy ..... 364&#13;
Petra Menz &amp; Nicola Mulberry: Open Source Differential and Integral Calculus Material Development to Support Student Accessibility and Learning ..... 368&#13;
Claus Michelsen: The MACAS Symposiums 2005 – 2019. Mathematics Education in an Interdisciplinary Context ..... 374&#13;
Marguerite K. Miheso-O’Connor: Teaching Mathematics through Historic Environment. A Time-Travel Grounded Pedagogy ..... 380&#13;
Jenny Missen: Researching and Implementing in the Mathematics Classroom Australian Curriculum General Capabilities ..... 386&#13;
Shelby Morge: Addressing Teachers’ Culturally Responsive Teaching Beliefs through Course Activities ..... 392&#13;
Janina Morska: From the Purpose of the Lesson to Success ..... 398&#13;
Lio Moscardini et al: Collaborating Across the Pond: Cognitively Guided Instruction Project ..... 401&#13;
Nitsa Movshovitz-Hadar et al: Bridging between School Mathematics and Contemporary Mathematics: Turning a Dream into Reality ..... 406&#13;
Ajayagosh Narayanan: Peer Tutoring: Developing and Sustaining Effective Teaching Practices with Mathematics Teachers in Lesotho ..... 412&#13;
María Estela Navarro Robles: Variation Theory used to make a Personalized Diagnostic in the Level of Knowledge of Fundamental Concepts about Rational Numbers and their Operations in Undergraduate Students ..... 418&#13;
Margaret L. Niess: Online Strategies Enhancing Mathematics Teacher Knowledge for the Digital Age: Discourse and Critical Reflection  ..... 422&#13;
Jenna R. O’Dell &amp; Todd R. Frauenholtz: An Unsolved Graph Theory Problem: Comparing Solutions of Grades 4, 6, &amp; 8 ..... 428&#13;
Niamh O’Meara &amp; Fiona Faulkner: Professional Development for Out-of-field Post-primary Teachers of Mathematics: A pre and post Analysis of the Impact of Mathematics Specific Pedagogical Training ..... 434&#13;
Jenny Pagge: Effective Use of ICT and Storytelling to Teach Statistics in the Preschool Classroom ..... 440&#13;
Catherine Paolucci: Supporting Pre-service Mathematics Teacher Development through Transformative Community Engagement ..... 445&#13;
Catherine Pearn et al: Developing and Assessing Algebraic Reasoning in the Middle Years ..... 450&#13;
Esther Pearson: “STEPS” to a Brighter Future ..... 456&#13;
Mary E. Pilgrim &amp; Thomas P. Dick: Actively Engaging in Calculus to Support all Students ..... 462&#13;
Ildikó-Anna Pomuczné Nagy: How and where can a Mathematics Teacher Utilize his 33 Years of Teaching Experience? A Math Teacher about Teaching Mathematics-Excerpt from 33 Years of Teaching Experience ..... 467&#13;
Hilary Povey: Moral and Political Dilemmas in Working with the Concept of Citizenship within Mathematics Teaching in Schools: a Personal Perspective ..... 473&#13;
Mark Prendergast et al: Incentivising the Study of Higher Level Mathematics ..... 479&#13;
Shagufta Raja et al: Using GIS to Develop Spatial Reasoning and Analysis of Data ..... 485&#13;
John R. Ramsay: Mentored Teams of Undergraduates in Real World Consulting ..... 491&#13;
Marina Rugelj: Counting with 10 Fingers as a Man, with 8 fingers as a Hen or with 2 Switches on a Computer ..... 497&#13;
Jacqueline Sack &amp; Judith Quander: Secondary Math Teacher Candidates’ Perspectives on a Co-Taught Blended Content &amp; Methods Geometry Course ..... 503&#13;
Adalira Sáenz-Ludlow &amp; Alexandra Jiménez Jiménez: Linkages between a Teacher’s Preparation and the Potential for Students’ Learning ..... 509&#13;
S. R. Santhanam: Welcome 2019 – A Workshop on Framing Non-Routine Problems in Mathematics for all Levels ..... 515&#13;
Josephine Shamash: From Equations to Structures: Linking Abstract Algebra and High-School Algebra for Secondary School Teachers ..... 517&#13;
Dennis Showers: Real-world Maths: Preparing Teachers to use Real-life Contexts for Teaching Maths ..... 523&#13;
Atara Shriki &amp; Ilana Lavy: Shedding New Light on Common Algorithms: What can we Learn from the Vedic Mathematics? ..... 526&#13;
Timothy Sibbald: The Confluence of Numeracy with Interdisciplinary Mathematics ..... 529&#13;
Dianne Siemon: Connecting Research and Practice – The Case of Multiplicative Thinking ..... 535&#13;
Raymond Smith et al: Insights Gained from Implementing Teaching Toolkits: A Case of Activating Prior Knowledge ..... 541&#13;
Kerri Spooner: Authentic Mathematical Modelling Behaviours for Secondary School Students ..... 547&#13;
Max Stephens: Developing Algorithmic Thinking in Mathematics in the Primary and Junior Secondary Years ..... 552&#13;
Tadashi Takahashi: Proving in Mathematics Education - On the Proof using ATP -  ..... 558 &#13;
David Tannor: Effective Mathematics Instruction: Two-Year College Mathematics Instructors’ Knowledge and Self-Efficacy ..... 564&#13;
Barbara Ann Temple et al: Designing a Transdisciplinary Approach to Elementary Math Literacy Learning through Science &amp; the Arts ..... 570&#13;
Jeffrey Thomas: Learning through Self-Assessment towards Understanding the New B.Ed. Curriculum in South Africa: Experiences from the new B.Ed. Programme at Sol Plaatje University ..... 575&#13;
José A. Toro-Clarke: A Participative and Individualized Laboratory: A Strategy for Increasing Student Success in College-Level Math Courses ..... 581&#13;
Ariana-Stanca Vacaretu: Developing High-school Students’ Competences through Math Research Workshops – the M&amp;L Project ..... 587&#13;
Thomas Walsh Jr: Exploring Computer Science with MicroworldsEX to Learn Geometry and Logo Programming Code ..... 593&#13;
Thomas Walsh Jr.: The Survey Toolkit Curriculum Methodology for Researching Information, Survey Questioning, and Analyzing Data with TinkerPlots ..... 599&#13;
Lynae Warren &amp; Kay Wohlhuter: Merging Theory and Practice in Statistics in Communities of Mathematical Inquiry ..... 605&#13;
Steven Watson: Bridging Theory and Practice: a Posthuman Perspective on Mathematics Teacher Education ..... 607&#13;
Lyn Webb et al: Enabling Grade 3 Teachers to Transform an Intended Curriculum into an Enacted Curriculum in Mathematics Classrooms ..... 613&#13;
Paul Webb: Towards a Unifying Logic for the Pedagogy of Mathematics in South Africa ..... 618&#13;
Gregory A. Wickliff et al:Communicating Mathematics and Science: Teaching and Tutoring Writing in a Summer Program for High School Students ..... 623&#13;
Ian Willson: Formative Assessment and Middle-school Classroom Tasks with the Wolfram Language ..... 629&#13;
Stephen Woodcock: Not all Equals are Equal: Decoupling Thinking Processes and Results in Mathematical Assessments ..... 631&#13;
Simon Zell: Weekly 10-minute-tasks to Promote Students Solving Equations in a Content-oriented Manner ..... 637&#13;
Alan Zollman: Collective Participation: A Story of Business, Community, Schools, and University Partnering in STEM Education ..... 643&#13;
Ryan G. Zonnefeld &amp; Valorie L. Zonnefeld: Innovative Pathways in STEM Teacher Preparation: Bridging the Gap between University Expectations &amp; Secondary School Needs ..... 649&#13;
Deserving Scholars &amp; Researchers, Maynooth, 2019 ..... 652</mods:tableOfContents>
                  <mods:targetAudience>specialized</mods:targetAudience>
                  <mods:note type="content">Druckausgabe: Rogerson, Alan; Morska, Janina (Hrsg.): The Mathematics Education for the Future Project – Proceedings of the 15th International Conference. Münster : WTM, 2019. (Conference Proceedings in Mathematics Education ; 4), ISBN 978-3-95987-111-2</mods:note>
                  <mods:note type="ownership">© 2019 WTM – Verlag für wissenschaftliche Texte und Medien, Münster</mods:note>
                  <mods:subject>
                    <mods:topic lang="ger">Affekt; Analysis; Beweisen; Bruchrechnung; Computeralgebrasystem; Eulerdreieck; GeoGebra; Kognition; Lehrerausbildung; Mathematikdidaktik; Serious Game</mods:topic>
                  </mods:subject>
                  <mods:classification authority="ddc">370</mods:classification>
                  <mods:classification authority="ddc">510</mods:classification>
                  <mods:relatedItem type="series">
                    <mods:titleInfo>
                      <mods:title script="Latn">Conference proceedings in mathematics education</mods:title>
                    </mods:titleInfo>
                    <mods:part type="volume" order="4">
                      <mods:detail>
                        <mods:number>4</mods:number>
                      </mods:detail>
                    </mods:part>
                    <mods:recordInfo>
                      <mods:recordIdentifier>oai:wwu.de:4cb868bf-7636-49d7-82fa-a70f54b19631</mods:recordIdentifier>
                    </mods:recordInfo>
                  </mods:relatedItem>
                  <mods:identifier type="urn">urn:nbn:de:hbz:6-44119506495</mods:identifier>
                  <mods:identifier type="isbn">978-3-95987-112-9</mods:identifier>
                  <mods:location>
                    <mods:url access="object in context">https://miami.uni-muenster.de/Record/a80ac83f-a3d6-4154-9345-5318eb9d15a6</mods:url>
                  </mods:location>
                  <mods:accessCondition type="restriction on access">
                    <mods:extension>
                      <ma:maWrap xmlns:ma="http://memoryalpha.ulb.uni-muenster.de">
                        <ma:licence>
                          <ma:displayLabel>InC 1.0</ma:displayLabel>
                          <ma:targetUrl>https://rightsstatements.org/vocab/InC/1.0/</ma:targetUrl>
                        </ma:licence>
                      </ma:maWrap>
                    </mods:extension>
                  </mods:accessCondition>
                  <mods:recordInfo>
                    <mods:recordIdentifier>oai:wwu.de:a80ac83f-a3d6-4154-9345-5318eb9d15a6</mods:recordIdentifier>
                  </mods:recordInfo>
                </mods:mods>
              </mets:xmlData>
            </mets:mdWrap>
          </mets:dmdSec>
          <mets:amdSec ID="AMD_a80ac83f-a3d6-4154-9345-5318eb9d15a6">
            <mets:rightsMD ID="RIGHTSMD_a80ac83f-a3d6-4154-9345-5318eb9d15a6">
              <mets:mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" MIMETYPE="text/xml" OTHERMDTYPE="DVRIGHTS">
                <mets:xmlData>
                  <dv:rights xmlns:dv="http://dfg-viewer.de/">
                    <dv:owner>Universitäts- und Landesbibliothek Münster</dv:owner>
                  </dv:rights>
                </mets:xmlData>
              </mets:mdWrap>
            </mets:rightsMD>
            <mets:digiprovMD ID="DIGIPROVMD_a80ac83f-a3d6-4154-9345-5318eb9d15a6">
              <mets:mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" MIMETYPE="text/xml" OTHERMDTYPE="DVLINKS">
                <mets:xmlData>
                  <dv:links xmlns:dv="http://dfg-viewer.de/">
                    <dv:reference>https://miami.uni-muenster.de/Record/a80ac83f-a3d6-4154-9345-5318eb9d15a6</dv:reference>
                    <dv:presentation/>
                  </dv:links>
                </mets:xmlData>
              </mets:mdWrap>
            </mets:digiprovMD>
          </mets:amdSec>
          <mets:fileSec>
            <mets:fileGrp USE="DEFAULT">
              <mets:file MIMETYPE="application/pdf" CHECKSUM="73fa3052787639da00a6dc15931dc8c141391a9a8e39f2e0cd9d1be8001edd7e" CREATED="2022-04-07T10:48:41" CHECKSUMTYPE="SHA-256" SIZE="17030789" ID="ID_FIL_wtm_isbn_978-3-95987-112-9.pdf_DEFAULT">
                <mets:FLocat xlink:href="https://repositorium.uni-muenster.de/document/miami/a80ac83f-a3d6-4154-9345-5318eb9d15a6/wtm_isbn_978-3-95987-112-9.pdf" LOCTYPE="URL"/>
              </mets:file>
            </mets:fileGrp>
            <mets:fileGrp USE="DOWNLOAD">
              <mets:file MIMETYPE="application/pdf" ID="DOWa80ac83f-a3d6-4154-9345-5318eb9d15a6">
                <mets:FLocat xlink:href="https://repositorium.uni-muenster.de/transfer/miami/a80ac83f-a3d6-4154-9345-5318eb9d15a6" LOCTYPE="URL"/>
              </mets:file>
            </mets:fileGrp>
          </mets:fileSec>
          <mets:structMap TYPE="PHYSICAL">
            <mets:div ID="ID_PHY_a80ac83f-a3d6-4154-9345-5318eb9d15a6" TYPE="physSequence">
              <mets:div ID="ID_PHY_wtm_isbn_978-3-95987-112-9.pdf">
                <mets:fptr FILEID="ID_FIL_wtm_isbn_978-3-95987-112-9.pdf_DEFAULT"/>
              </mets:div>
            </mets:div>
          </mets:structMap>
          <mets:structMap TYPE="LOGICAL">
            <mets:div ADMID="AMD_a80ac83f-a3d6-4154-9345-5318eb9d15a6" DMDID="DMD_a80ac83f-a3d6-4154-9345-5318eb9d15a6" ID="ID_LOG_a80ac83f-a3d6-4154-9345-5318eb9d15a6" TYPE="Monograph">
              <mets:div ID="ID_LOG_ID_PHY_wtm_isbn_978-3-95987-112-9.pdf"/>
            </mets:div>
          </mets:structMap>
          <mets:structLink>
            <mets:smLink xlink:from="ID_LOG_a80ac83f-a3d6-4154-9345-5318eb9d15a6" xlink:to="ID_PHY_a80ac83f-a3d6-4154-9345-5318eb9d15a6"/>
            <mets:smLink xlink:from="ID_LOG_ID_PHY_wtm_isbn_978-3-95987-112-9.pdf" xlink:to="ID_PHY_wtm_isbn_978-3-95987-112-9.pdf"/>
          </mets:structLink>
        </mets:mets>