<mets:mets xmlns:mets="http://www.loc.gov/METS/" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/METS/ https://www.loc.gov/standards/mets/mets.xsd" OBJID="oai:wwu.de:e8c7dc98-0ae5-4396-9ea9-a0ace14d5a22" LABEL="University of Muenster, Institutional Repository MIAMI"  xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
          <mets:metsHdr CREATEDATE="2022-04-07T09:38:17">
            <mets:agent TYPE="OTHER" ROLE="OTHER" OTHERTYPE="SOFTWARE">
              <mets:name>Memory Alpha</mets:name>
            </mets:agent>
          </mets:metsHdr>
          <mets:dmdSec ID="DMD_e8c7dc98-0ae5-4396-9ea9-a0ace14d5a22">
            <mets:mdWrap MIMETYPE="text/xml" MDTYPE="MODS">
              <mets:xmlData>
                <mods:mods xmlns:mods="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-7.xsd" version="3.7">
                  <mods:titleInfo type="uniform" lang="eng">
                    <mods:title script="Latn">Educating the educators: international approaches to scaling-up professional development in mathematics and science education</mods:title>
                    <mods:subTitle>proceedings of the conference hosted jointly by project mascil (mathematics and science for life) and the German Centre for Mathematics Education (DZLM), 15 -16 December 2014 in Essen, Germany</mods:subTitle>
                  </mods:titleInfo>
                  <mods:name type="personal" valueURI="http://d-nb.info/gnd/132602350">
                    <mods:namePart type="given">Katja</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:namePart type="family">Maaß</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:displayForm>Maaß, Katja</mods:displayForm>
                    <mods:role>
                      <mods:roleTerm type="code" authority="marcrelator">own</mods:roleTerm>
                    </mods:role>
                  </mods:name>
                  <mods:name type="corporate" valueURI="http://d-nb.info/gnd/5091030-9" altRepGroup="2">
                    <mods:namePart>Universitäts- und Landesbibliothek Münster</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:role>
                      <mods:roleTerm type="code" authority="marcrelator">own</mods:roleTerm>
                    </mods:role>
                  </mods:name>
                  <mods:name type="corporate" valueURI="http://d-nb.info/gnd/5091030-9" altRepGroup="2">
                    <mods:namePart>ULB Münster</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:role>
                      <mods:roleTerm type="code" authority="marcrelator">own</mods:roleTerm>
                    </mods:role>
                  </mods:name>
                  <mods:name type="corporate" valueURI="http://d-nb.info/gnd/5091030-9" altRepGroup="2">
                    <mods:namePart>Landesbibliothek Münster / Universitäts- und Landesbibliothek Münster</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:role>
                      <mods:roleTerm type="code" authority="marcrelator">own</mods:roleTerm>
                    </mods:role>
                  </mods:name>
                  <mods:name type="corporate" valueURI="http://d-nb.info/gnd/5091030-9" altRepGroup="2">
                    <mods:namePart>Universität Münster / Universitäts- und Landesbibliothek</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:role>
                      <mods:roleTerm type="code" authority="marcrelator">own</mods:roleTerm>
                    </mods:role>
                  </mods:name>
                  <mods:name type="personal" valueURI="http://d-nb.info/gnd/131661507">
                    <mods:namePart type="given">Karen</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:namePart type="family">Reitz-Koncebovski</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:displayForm>Reitz-Koncebovski, Karen</mods:displayForm>
                    <mods:role>
                      <mods:roleTerm type="code" authority="marcrelator">edt</mods:roleTerm>
                    </mods:role>
                  </mods:name>
                  <mods:name type="personal" valueURI="http://d-nb.info/gnd/124031935" altRepGroup="4">
                    <mods:namePart type="given">Bärbel</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:namePart type="family">Barzel</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:namePart type="date">1959-</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:displayForm>Barzel, Bärbel</mods:displayForm>
                    <mods:affiliation>Zentrum für Lehrerbildung</mods:affiliation>
                    <mods:role>
                      <mods:roleTerm type="code" authority="marcrelator">edt</mods:roleTerm>
                    </mods:role>
                  </mods:name>
                  <mods:name type="personal" valueURI="http://d-nb.info/gnd/124031935" altRepGroup="4">
                    <mods:namePart type="given">B.</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:namePart type="family">Barzel</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:namePart type="date">1959-</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:displayForm>Barzel, B.</mods:displayForm>
                    <mods:affiliation>Zentrum für Lehrerbildung</mods:affiliation>
                    <mods:role>
                      <mods:roleTerm type="code" authority="marcrelator">edt</mods:roleTerm>
                    </mods:role>
                  </mods:name>
                  <mods:name type="personal" valueURI="http://d-nb.info/gnd/1115742663">
                    <mods:namePart type="given">Günter</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:namePart type="family">Törner</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:namePart type="date">1947-</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:displayForm>Törner, Günter</mods:displayForm>
                    <mods:role>
                      <mods:roleTerm type="code" authority="marcrelator">edt</mods:roleTerm>
                    </mods:role>
                  </mods:name>
                  <mods:name type="personal" valueURI="http://d-nb.info/gnd/1076822053">
                    <mods:namePart type="given">Diana</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:namePart type="family">Wernisch</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:displayForm>Wernisch, Diana</mods:displayForm>
                    <mods:role>
                      <mods:roleTerm type="code" authority="marcrelator">edt</mods:roleTerm>
                    </mods:role>
                  </mods:name>
                  <mods:name type="personal" valueURI="http://d-nb.info/gnd/14022467X">
                    <mods:namePart type="given">Elena</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:namePart type="family">Schäfer</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:displayForm>Schäfer, Elena</mods:displayForm>
                    <mods:role>
                      <mods:roleTerm type="code" authority="marcrelator">edt</mods:roleTerm>
                    </mods:role>
                  </mods:name>
                  <mods:genre>conferenceObject</mods:genre>
                  <mods:genre authority="dct">Text</mods:genre>
                  <mods:originInfo>
                    <mods:publisher>WTM-Verlag für wissenschaftliche Texte und Medien</mods:publisher>
                    <mods:dateIssued keyDate="yes">2015</mods:dateIssued>
                    <mods:issuance>monographic</mods:issuance>
                  </mods:originInfo>
                  <mods:originInfo>
                    <mods:dateIssued encoding="w3cdtf">2016-02-05</mods:dateIssued>
                    <mods:dateModified encoding="w3cdtf">2017-01-30</mods:dateModified>
                    <mods:edition>[Electronic ed.]</mods:edition>
                  </mods:originInfo>
                  <mods:language>
                    <mods:languageTerm type="code" authority="iso639-2b">eng</mods:languageTerm>
                  </mods:language>
                  <mods:physicalDescription>
                    <mods:form>electronic</mods:form>
                    <mods:reformattingQuality>access</mods:reformattingQuality>
                    <mods:internetMediaType>application/pdf</mods:internetMediaType>
                    <mods:extent>IV, 329</mods:extent>
                    <mods:digitalOrigin>born digital</mods:digitalOrigin>
                  </mods:physicalDescription>
                  <mods:abstract lang="eng">Teachers are the decisive factors in ensuring the achievement of creative and sustainable learning outcomes in mathematics and science education, in fostering young peoples’ competences and enabling them to become critically thinking, responsible and active citizens. Teacher professional development (PD) is the key to effecting change in mathematics and science education throughout Europe. Whilst the relevance of teacher PD is beyond dispute, there is still too little knowledge about how to scale-up professional development successfully and sustainably. &lt;br&gt;Initiating discourse and leveraging international exchange about concepts and experiences concerning this essential topic were the main aims of the conference ‘Educating the Educators – International approaches to scaling-up professional development in mathematics and science education’, which took place in December 2014 in Essen, Germany. &lt;br&gt;The conference was hosted by the EUfunded project mascil (mathematics and science for life), coordinated at the University of Freiburg, Germany, and the DZLM (German Centre for Mathematics Teacher Education) and brought together researchers and practitioners: teacher educators, multipliers and teachers who are all engaged in the field of maths and science education. This volume reflects participants’ conference experiences.</mods:abstract>
                  <mods:tableOfContents lang="eng">1 Conference: Educating the educators (K. Maass, D. Wernisch, K. Reitz-Koncebovski, E. Schäfer) ..... 5&#13;
1.1 Aims and objectives ..... 5&#13;
1.2 Conference tracks: Four different means of scaling-up ..... 6&#13;
1.2.1 Track 1: Scaling-up with multipliers in face-to-face professional development courses ..... 6&#13;
1.2.2 Track 2: Blended learning concepts and e-learning support ..... 7&#13;
1.2.3 Track 3: Disseminating and scaling-up through materials ..... 8&#13;
1.2.4 Track 4: Professional learning communities ..... 9&#13;
&#13;
2 Conference outcomes and conclusions (K. Maass, D. Wernisch, E. Schäfer) ..... 11&#13;
2.1 Teacher professional development: Europe-wide perspective on current needs and trends ..... 11&#13;
2.2 Bringing together a unique circle of participants: researchers, practitioners and policy makers ..... 11&#13;
2.3 Innovation: Establishment of a future-oriented, European network of teacher training centres ..... 12&#13;
2.4 mascil and DZLM - combining research and practice ..... 13&#13;
2.5 Trends and needs in Europe to scale-up teacher professional development ..... 15&#13;
&#13;
3 Conference Hosts ..... 18&#13;
3.1 mascil: maths and science for life! (K. Maass, D. Wernisch, E. Schäfer, A.-M. Aldorf) ..... 18&#13;
3.2 DZLM: German Centre for Mathematics Teacher Education DZLM Team ..... 23&#13;
&#13;
4 Keynotes: Abstracts and Speaker Information ..... 25&#13;
Scaling-up professional development: chances and challenges (K. Krainer) ..... 25&#13;
The role of informal science institutions in teacher education (J. Dillon) ..... 26&#13;
Teacher professional development in Europe: perceptions, policies, and practices (P. Birch) ..... 27&#13;
&#13;
5 Presenter Programme ..... 28&#13;
5.1 Track 1 plenary: Scaling-up with multipliers in face-to face professional development courses ..... 28&#13;
Long-term Teacher Professional Development: Lessons learnt from PRIMAS (J. Farrugia) ..... 28&#13;
5.2 Track 2 plenary: Blended learning concepts and e-learning support ..... 30&#13;
Blended learning and e-learning support within the context of Cornerstone Maths – The changing culture of teachers' professional development (A. Clark-Wilson) ..... 30&#13;
5.3 Track 3 plenary: Disseminating and scaling-up through materials ..... 32&#13;
Prepared to use it? – Disseminating and Scaling-up Professional Development Through Materials (M. Welzel-Breuer) ..... 32&#13;
5.4 Track 4 plenary: Professional learning communities ..... 34&#13;
Learning on three levels – students’, teachers’ and educators’ learning from the Learning study (U. Runesson) ..... 34&#13;
&#13;
6 Papers ..... 35&#13;
6.1 Track 1: Scaling-up with multipliers in face-to-face professional development courses ..... 35&#13;
Professional Development of experienced Teachers (H. J. Brenner) ..... 35&#13;
Building capacity: developing a course for mathematics and science teacher educators (A. Childs, J. Hillier, S. Thornton, A. Watson) ..... 47&#13;
PRIMAS Multiplier Concept Implementation in Slovakian Context (S. Čeretková, I. Jakab, Z. Naštická) ..... 56&#13;
Professionalizing teachers in a Teacher Design Team (F. Coenders) ..... 66&#13;
Long-term Teacher Professional Development: Lessons learnt from PRIMAS (J. Farrugia) ..... 72&#13;
KeyCoMath - Multipliers Concept for the Urban Network of Primary Schools (C. Götz, P. Ihn-Huber, V. Ulm) ..... 88&#13;
Sustainable Training in Mathematics (H. Juen, C. Juen-Kretschmer) ..... 92&#13;
Scaling up professional development: Changes and challenges (K. Krainer) ..... 96&#13;
KOMMS: Teacher training courses fostering modelling in schools (J. Kreckler) ..... 111&#13;
Inquiry based biology education in the Czech Republic: A reflection of five years dissemination (J. Petr, T. Ditrich, R. Závodská; M. Papáček) ..... 118&#13;
How to determine what teachers should learn and multipliers need to know? Five steps for content specification of professional development programs and the research-based background for multipliers (S. Prediger) ..... 125&#13;
&#13;
6.2 Track 2: Blended learning concepts and e-learning support ...... 127&#13;
A study and research path on mathematical modelling for inservice teacher education: the challenge of an online course on SRP-TE (B. Barquero, M. Bosch, A. Romo) ..... 127&#13;
Promoting teacher trainees’ inquiry skills by self-regulation and tablets (T. Bruckermann, E. Aschermann, A. Bresges, K. Schlüter) ..... 135&#13;
Online training courses: Design models, addressees, effects, and outstanding issues (R. Bruder, A. Böhnke) ..... 147&#13;
Blended learning and e-learning support within the Cornerstone Maths Project (A. Clark- Wilson, C. Hoyles) ..... 158&#13;
A Virtual Mathematics Laboratory in support of educating educators in inquiry-based style (P. Kenderov, T. Chehlarova, E. Sendova) ..... 167&#13;
Supporting the teacher role during amusement park visits: Materials, workshops and interaction (A.-M. Pendrill, C. Kozma, A. Theve) ..... 177&#13;
Using Blended Learning in a Math Pedagogy Course for Experienced Teachers (T. van den Bogaart) ..... 181&#13;
&#13;
6.3 Track 3: Disseminating and scaling-up through materials ......... 193&#13;
Learning through inquiry in the world of work at Primary School (M. R. Ariza, A. Quesada, A. M. Abril, M. Evagorou) ..... 193&#13;
An IBL application from the inside (C. Choutou, C. Kotteakos, V. Vonta, M. A. Zisimopoulou) ..... 199&#13;
Science and Maths by inquiring about the image size in a camera obscura (A. M. Criado, A. García-Carmona) ..... 210&#13;
The potential of a task for professional development across national contexts (M. Doorman, J. Garcia, D. Potari, G. Zsombori, S. András) ..... 216&#13;
Professional development of teachers by developing, testing and teaching curriculum materials of an interdisciplinary STEM-course (NLT) for senior high school (B. Michels, H. Eijkelhof) ..... 228&#13;
Raising the professional competence of mathematics teachers in Sweden: The challenges of practice viewed from a material developer’s perspective (O. Popov) ..... 234&#13;
Integrating inquiry-based tasks and the world of work in mathematics and science teacher education (D. Potari, G. Psycharis, V. Spiliotopoulou, C. Triantafillou, T. Zachariades) ..... 240&#13;
&#13;
6.4 Track 4: Professional learning communities ..... 255&#13;
Using video recordings of ones own lessons – supporting teachers by coaching lesson development (G. Bieber, E. Binner) ..... 255&#13;
Teacher PD in the Czech Republic and implications of mascil (M. Bílek, I. Šimonová, M. Maněnová) ..... 259&#13;
Professional qualification of teacher tandems conceptually combined with lesson development (M. Grassmann, E. Binner) ..... 267&#13;
Competencies in Mathematics and Science Education (CMSE): A programme promoting in-service teachers’ professional development (C. Haagen, V. Rechberger, W. Knechtl, G. Rath, L. Mathelitsch) ..... 273&#13;
Professional Learning Communities: What are the important questions for an educator to ensure a sustainable community? (C. Pearn) ..... 279&#13;
Professional Learning Communities - the case of Learning study (U. Runesson) ..... 291&#13;
A study of collaboration between mathematics teachers and mathematics education researchers: insights into developing professional learning (K. Siopi, A. Chatzigoula, A. Manaridis, D. Potari, C. Sakonidis) ..... 301&#13;
Learning Communities in a STEM Education Network: scaling-up a talent development programme (T. van der Valk, S. Sanne Tromp, C. Kleijer) ..... 304&#13;
Lesson Study as a tool for professional development: the context of counting problems (N. Verhoef, F. Coenders) ..... 316&#13;
Content focused peer coaching and the development of lesson plans about scientific inquiry (H. Weitzel, R. Blank) ..... 325</mods:tableOfContents>
                  <mods:targetAudience>specialized</mods:targetAudience>
                  <mods:note type="content">Druckausg.: Maaß, Katja (Hrsg.): Educating the educators: international approaches to scaling-up professional development in mathematics and science education : proceedings of the conference hosted jointly by project mascil (mathematics and science for life) and the German Centre for Mathematics Education (DZLM), 15 -16 December 2014 in Essen, Germany. Münster : WTM, 2015. (Conference Proceedings in Mathematics Education ; 2), ISBN 978-3-942197-77-9</mods:note>
                  <mods:note type="ownership">© 2015 WTM – Verlag für wissenschaftliche Texte und Medien, Münster</mods:note>
                  <mods:subject>
                    <mods:topic lang="ger">Lehrerbildung ; Lehrerfortbildung ; Mathematikunterricht ; Naturwissenschaftlicher Unterricht ; Kongress, Essen &lt;2014&gt;</mods:topic>
                  </mods:subject>
                  <mods:classification authority="ddc">510</mods:classification>
                  <mods:classification authority="ddc">370</mods:classification>
                  <mods:relatedItem type="series">
                    <mods:titleInfo>
                      <mods:title script="Latn">Conference proceedings in mathematics education</mods:title>
                    </mods:titleInfo>
                    <mods:part type="volume" order="2">
                      <mods:detail>
                        <mods:number>2</mods:number>
                      </mods:detail>
                    </mods:part>
                    <mods:recordInfo>
                      <mods:recordIdentifier>oai:wwu.de:4cb868bf-7636-49d7-82fa-a70f54b19631</mods:recordIdentifier>
                    </mods:recordInfo>
                  </mods:relatedItem>
                  <mods:identifier type="urn">urn:nbn:de:hbz:6-66299622904</mods:identifier>
                  <mods:identifier type="isbn">978-3-942197-85-4</mods:identifier>
                  <mods:location>
                    <mods:url access="object in context">https://miami.uni-muenster.de/Record/e8c7dc98-0ae5-4396-9ea9-a0ace14d5a22</mods:url>
                  </mods:location>
                  <mods:accessCondition type="restriction on access">
                    <mods:extension>
                      <ma:maWrap xmlns:ma="http://memoryalpha.ulb.uni-muenster.de">
                        <ma:licence>
                          <ma:displayLabel>InC 1.0</ma:displayLabel>
                          <ma:targetUrl>https://rightsstatements.org/vocab/InC/1.0/</ma:targetUrl>
                        </ma:licence>
                      </ma:maWrap>
                    </mods:extension>
                  </mods:accessCondition>
                  <mods:recordInfo>
                    <mods:recordIdentifier>oai:wwu.de:e8c7dc98-0ae5-4396-9ea9-a0ace14d5a22</mods:recordIdentifier>
                  </mods:recordInfo>
                </mods:mods>
              </mets:xmlData>
            </mets:mdWrap>
          </mets:dmdSec>
          <mets:amdSec ID="AMD_e8c7dc98-0ae5-4396-9ea9-a0ace14d5a22">
            <mets:rightsMD ID="RIGHTSMD_e8c7dc98-0ae5-4396-9ea9-a0ace14d5a22">
              <mets:mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" MIMETYPE="text/xml" OTHERMDTYPE="DVRIGHTS">
                <mets:xmlData>
                  <dv:rights xmlns:dv="http://dfg-viewer.de/">
                    <dv:owner>Universitäts- und Landesbibliothek Münster</dv:owner>
                  </dv:rights>
                </mets:xmlData>
              </mets:mdWrap>
            </mets:rightsMD>
            <mets:digiprovMD ID="DIGIPROVMD_e8c7dc98-0ae5-4396-9ea9-a0ace14d5a22">
              <mets:mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" MIMETYPE="text/xml" OTHERMDTYPE="DVLINKS">
                <mets:xmlData>
                  <dv:links xmlns:dv="http://dfg-viewer.de/">
                    <dv:reference>https://miami.uni-muenster.de/Record/e8c7dc98-0ae5-4396-9ea9-a0ace14d5a22</dv:reference>
                    <dv:presentation/>
                  </dv:links>
                </mets:xmlData>
              </mets:mdWrap>
            </mets:digiprovMD>
          </mets:amdSec>
          <mets:fileSec>
            <mets:fileGrp USE="DEFAULT">
              <mets:file MIMETYPE="application/pdf" CHECKSUM="a9d19240ca3619cfb26ada2bcb448e76707b6a9b269d2c9b811bceef1befa024" CREATED="2017-01-30T15:33:21" CHECKSUMTYPE="SHA-256" SIZE="10731290" ID="ID_FIL_wtm_isbn-978-3-942197-85-4.pdf_DEFAULT">
                <mets:FLocat xlink:href="https://repositorium.uni-muenster.de/document/miami/e8c7dc98-0ae5-4396-9ea9-a0ace14d5a22/wtm_isbn-978-3-942197-85-4.pdf" LOCTYPE="URL"/>
              </mets:file>
            </mets:fileGrp>
            <mets:fileGrp USE="DOWNLOAD">
              <mets:file MIMETYPE="application/pdf" ID="DOWe8c7dc98-0ae5-4396-9ea9-a0ace14d5a22">
                <mets:FLocat xlink:href="https://repositorium.uni-muenster.de/transfer/miami/e8c7dc98-0ae5-4396-9ea9-a0ace14d5a22" LOCTYPE="URL"/>
              </mets:file>
            </mets:fileGrp>
          </mets:fileSec>
          <mets:structMap TYPE="PHYSICAL">
            <mets:div ID="ID_PHY_e8c7dc98-0ae5-4396-9ea9-a0ace14d5a22" TYPE="physSequence">
              <mets:div ID="ID_PHY_wtm_isbn-978-3-942197-85-4.pdf">
                <mets:fptr FILEID="ID_FIL_wtm_isbn-978-3-942197-85-4.pdf_DEFAULT"/>
              </mets:div>
            </mets:div>
          </mets:structMap>
          <mets:structMap TYPE="LOGICAL">
            <mets:div ADMID="AMD_e8c7dc98-0ae5-4396-9ea9-a0ace14d5a22" DMDID="DMD_e8c7dc98-0ae5-4396-9ea9-a0ace14d5a22" ID="ID_LOG_e8c7dc98-0ae5-4396-9ea9-a0ace14d5a22" TYPE="Monograph">
              <mets:div ID="ID_LOG_ID_PHY_wtm_isbn-978-3-942197-85-4.pdf"/>
            </mets:div>
          </mets:structMap>
          <mets:structLink>
            <mets:smLink xlink:from="ID_LOG_e8c7dc98-0ae5-4396-9ea9-a0ace14d5a22" xlink:to="ID_PHY_e8c7dc98-0ae5-4396-9ea9-a0ace14d5a22"/>
            <mets:smLink xlink:from="ID_LOG_ID_PHY_wtm_isbn-978-3-942197-85-4.pdf" xlink:to="ID_PHY_wtm_isbn-978-3-942197-85-4.pdf"/>
          </mets:structLink>
        </mets:mets>