<mets:mets xmlns:mets="http://www.loc.gov/METS/" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/METS/ https://www.loc.gov/standards/mets/mets.xsd" OBJID="oai:wwu.de:5f210d40-7a28-4b7e-b8b6-9305c3a13337" LABEL="University of Muenster, Institutional Repository MIAMI"  xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
          <mets:metsHdr CREATEDATE="2022-11-09T15:02:59">
            <mets:agent TYPE="OTHER" ROLE="OTHER" OTHERTYPE="SOFTWARE">
              <mets:name>Memory Alpha</mets:name>
            </mets:agent>
          </mets:metsHdr>
          <mets:dmdSec ID="DMD_5f210d40-7a28-4b7e-b8b6-9305c3a13337">
            <mets:mdWrap MIMETYPE="text/xml" MDTYPE="MODS">
              <mets:xmlData>
                <mods:mods xmlns:mods="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-7.xsd" version="3.7">
                  <mods:titleInfo type="uniform" lang="eng">
                    <mods:title script="Latn">The Mathematics Education for the Future Project</mods:title>
                    <mods:subTitle>King's College, Cambridge Aug 8-13, 2022 : Proceedings of the 16th International Conference : Building on the Past to Prepare for the Future</mods:subTitle>
                  </mods:titleInfo>
                  <mods:name type="personal">
                    <mods:namePart type="given">Janina</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:namePart type="family">Morska</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:displayForm>Morska, Janina</mods:displayForm>
                    <mods:role>
                      <mods:roleTerm type="code" authority="marcrelator">edt</mods:roleTerm>
                    </mods:role>
                  </mods:name>
                  <mods:name type="personal">
                    <mods:namePart type="given">Alan</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:namePart type="family">Rogerson</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:displayForm>Rogerson, Alan</mods:displayForm>
                    <mods:role>
                      <mods:roleTerm type="code" authority="marcrelator">edt</mods:roleTerm>
                    </mods:role>
                  </mods:name>
                  <mods:name type="corporate" valueURI="http://d-nb.info/gnd/5091030-9" altRepGroup="3">
                    <mods:namePart>Universitäts- und Landesbibliothek Münster</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:role>
                      <mods:roleTerm type="code" authority="marcrelator">own</mods:roleTerm>
                    </mods:role>
                  </mods:name>
                  <mods:name type="corporate" valueURI="http://d-nb.info/gnd/5091030-9" altRepGroup="3">
                    <mods:namePart>Münster, Westfalen / ULB</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:role>
                      <mods:roleTerm type="code" authority="marcrelator">own</mods:roleTerm>
                    </mods:role>
                  </mods:name>
                  <mods:name type="corporate" valueURI="http://d-nb.info/gnd/5091030-9" altRepGroup="3">
                    <mods:namePart>Münster, Westfalen / Landesbibliothek</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:role>
                      <mods:roleTerm type="code" authority="marcrelator">own</mods:roleTerm>
                    </mods:role>
                  </mods:name>
                  <mods:name type="corporate" valueURI="http://d-nb.info/gnd/5091030-9" altRepGroup="3">
                    <mods:namePart>Westfalen / Universität Münster / Universitäts- und Landesbibliothek</mods:namePart>
                    <mods:role>
                      <mods:roleTerm type="code" authority="marcrelator">own</mods:roleTerm>
                    </mods:role>
                  </mods:name>
                  <mods:genre>conferenceObject</mods:genre>
                  <mods:genre authority="dct">Text</mods:genre>
                  <mods:originInfo>
                    <mods:publisher>WTM-Verlag für wissenschaftliche Texte und Medien</mods:publisher>
                    <mods:dateIssued keyDate="yes">2022</mods:dateIssued>
                    <mods:issuance>monographic</mods:issuance>
                  </mods:originInfo>
                  <mods:originInfo>
                    <mods:dateIssued encoding="w3cdtf">2022-07-01</mods:dateIssued>
                    <mods:dateModified encoding="w3cdtf">2022-07-01</mods:dateModified>
                    <mods:edition>[Electronic ed.]</mods:edition>
                  </mods:originInfo>
                  <mods:language>
                    <mods:languageTerm type="code" authority="iso639-2b">eng</mods:languageTerm>
                  </mods:language>
                  <mods:physicalDescription>
                    <mods:form>electronic</mods:form>
                    <mods:reformattingQuality>access</mods:reformattingQuality>
                    <mods:internetMediaType>application/pdf</mods:internetMediaType>
                    <mods:extent>xiii, 854</mods:extent>
                    <mods:digitalOrigin>born digital</mods:digitalOrigin>
                  </mods:physicalDescription>
                  <mods:abstract lang="eng">This volume contains the papers presented at the International Conference Building on the Past to Prepare for the Future held from August 8-13, 2022, in King’s College, Cambridge, UK. It was the 16th conference organised by The Mathematics Education for the Future Project - an international educational and philanthropic project founded in 1986 and dedicated to innovation in mathematics, statistics, science and computer education world wide.</mods:abstract>
                  <mods:tableOfContents lang="ger">Fouze Abu Qouder &amp; Miriam Amit | The Ethnomathematics of the Bedouin - An Innovative Approach of Integrating Socio Cultural Elements into Mathematics Education ..... 1&#13;
Nadine Adams &amp; Clinton Hayes | Why Everyone should know Statistics! ..... 7&#13;
Anita N. Alexander | The Perspectives of Effective Teaching and Learning of Current Undergraduate and Graduate Mathematics Students ..... 12&#13;
Clement Ayarebilla Ali &amp; Ernest Kofi Davis | Applications of Basketry to Geometric Tessellations ..... 18&#13;
Nurten Alpaslan &amp; Emre Alpaslan | Mathematics for Everybody ..... 24&#13;
Cynthia Oropesa Anhalt, Ricardo Cortez, Brynja Kohler &amp; Will Tidwell | Interrogation of Social Justice Contexts in Mathematical Modeling: The Use of Simulations of Practice in the Mathematical Preparation of Teachers ..... 26&#13;
Takako Aoki &amp; Shin Watanabe | Find out Mathematics on a Football: Making a football with Paper ..... 32&#13;
Sarah Bansilal | Analysing the Demands of an Assessment in a Geometry Pedagogic Content Knowledge Module ..... 35&#13;
Mike Bedwell | Three or Four numbers: A Teacher's Tale ..... 41&#13;
Esther Billings &amp; Lisa Kasmer | Learning Experiences that Support Primary Teacher Candidates' Understanding and Enactment of Core Mathematics Teaching Practices ..... 44&#13;
Victoria Bonaccorso, Joseph DiNapoli &amp; Eileen Murray | Promoting Meaningful Conversations among Prospective Mathematics Teachers ..... 50&#13;
Primo Brandi, Rita Ceppitelli &amp; Anna Salvadori | Elementary Dynamic Models: A Strategic Bridge Connecting School and University ..... 56&#13;
Simone Brasili &amp; Riccardo Piergallini | Introducing Symmetry and Invariance with Magic Squares ..... 63&#13;
Angela Broaddus &amp; Matthew Broaddus | Assessing Mathematical Reasoning: Test Less – Explain More ..... 69&#13;
Irena Budínová &amp; Jitka Panáčová | Children with Reduced Cognitive Effectivity, their Problems and Optimal Way of Education ..... 75&#13;
Gail Burrill | Data Science and Mathematical Modeling: Connecting Mathematics to the World in which Students Live ..... 81&#13;
Gail Burrill &amp; Thomas Dick | Connecting Mathematics to the World: Engaging Students with Data Science ..... 90&#13;
Elizabeth A. Burroughs &amp; Mary Alice Carlson | Fostering Empathy in Mathematics through Mathematical Modeling ..... 95&#13;
Bernardo Camou | The Adventure of Learning Mathematics and Lakatos's Legacy ..... 101&#13;
Carrie Chiappetta, Christopher Walsh, Annie Smith &amp; Javier Perez | K-12 Schools after the Global Pandemic: How a Regional School District in the United States Accelerated Learning for Students, Teachers &amp; Administrators ..... 105&#13;
Kathleen Cotter Clayton | Fractions of the Future ..... 111&#13;
Joan A. Cotter | Teaching Primary Mathematics without Counting and Place Value with Transparent Number Naming ..... 117&#13;
Celisa Counterman | M.A.T.H. = Making Algebraic Thinking Holistic ..... 123&#13;
Scott A. Courtney | The Impact of Remote Instruction on Mathematics Teachers' Practices ..... 128&#13;
Mili Das | Building on the Past to Prepare for the Future - Impact of Teaching Skills and Professionalism to Reduce Mathematics Phobia ..... 134&#13;
Thomas P. Dick | Combining Dynamic Computer Algebra and Geometry to Illustrate "the most marvelous theorem in mathematics" ..... 139&#13;
Hamide Dogan, Angel Garcia Contreras &amp; Edith Shear | Geometry, Imagery, and Cognition in Linear Algebra ..... 145&#13;
Ann Dowker, Olivia Cheriton &amp; Rachel Horton | Age Differences in Pupils' Attitudes to Mathematics ..... 151&#13;
Alden J. Edson &amp; Elizabeth Difanis Phillips | The Potential of Digital Collaborative Environments for Problem-Based&#13;
Mathematics Curriculum ..... 157&#13;
Belinda P. Edwards | Learning to Teach Mathematics using Virtual Reality Simulations ..... 163&#13;
Allison Elowson, Kristen Fye, Gregory Wickliff, Christopher Gordon, Alisa Wickliff, Paul Hunter &amp; David Pugalee | Student Research in a Mathematics Enrichment Program ..... 169&#13;
Antonella Fatai | Improving Relational and Disciplinary Competences by Rondine Method ..... 175&#13;
Courtney Fox | Integrating Mathematics and Science: A Plan for a High School Integrated Pre-Calculus and Physics Course ..... 181&#13;
Kathy R. Fox | Building an Understanding of Family Literacy: Changing Perspectives Regarding Authentic Learning Opportunities in the Home ..... 186&#13;
Grant A. Fraser | Mathematics for Living: A Course that Focuses on Solving Problems in Today's World ..... 192&#13;
Toshiakira Fujii | Roles of Quasi-variables in the Process of Discovering Mathematical Propositions ..... 196&#13;
Ben Galluzzo, Katie Kavanagh, Karen Bliss, Michelle Montgomery &amp; Christopher Musco | Math Modelling: Common Pitfalls and Paths for Student Success ..... .202&#13;
Parker Glynn-Adey &amp; Ami Mamolo | Modelling Beauty: Hands-on Experiences in Group Theory ..... 208&#13;
Gerald A. Goldin, Lisa B. Warner, Roberta Y. Schorr &amp; Daniel Colaneri | Exploring Prospective Mathematics Teachers' Motivating Desires during Group Problem Solving Activity ..... 214&#13;
John Gordon &amp; Kehinde Emmanuel Adenegan | Are Abstract Mathematical Thinkers Born or Can They Be Trained? ..... 220&#13;
John Gordon | Reuniting Exponents and Logarithms: Teaching Exponents, Inverse functions, and Logarithms, as one Cohesive Pedagogical Unit ..... 225&#13;
Debra Hydorn | Infographics to Develop Graphical Literacy ..... 231&#13;
Andrew Izsák | Foregrounding Multiplicative Structure in Essential Calculus Topics ..... 237&#13;
Brian L. Johnson &amp; Ioannis Gkigkitzis | Interesting Facts about Terminating Decimals ..... 243&#13;
Iris DeLoach Johnson | Exploring a Collection of Approachable, Stimulating and Thought-Provoking Problems: Face-to-Face or Virtual? Related or not? ..... 249&#13;
Gibbs Y. Kanyongo, Nandini Bhowmick &amp; Erika Williams | Structural Equation Modeling: Focus on Confirmatory Factor Analysis ..... 254&#13;
Anna Khalemsky &amp; Yelena Stukalin | Combining Various Data Mining Techniques in Binary Classification Teaching ..... 256&#13;
Richard Kitchen | Leveraging Pólya's Heuristic to Support Mathematical Reasoning and Language Development ..... 261&#13;
Sergiy Klymchuk | An Innovative Way of Teaching and Assessing Critical Thinking in Mathematics ..... 267&#13;
Allison M. Kroesch &amp; Albert Otto | Magic Throughout the Years ..... 273&#13;
Aradhana Kumari | Do not Teach the Symbols in Mathematics, Teach the Meaning of the Symbols ..... 277&#13;
Sebastian Kuntze, Marita Friesen, Jens Krummenauer, Karen Skilling, Ceneida Fernandez, Pere Ivars, Salvador Llinares, Libuše Samkova &amp; Lulu Healy | Support for Mathematics Teachers through Representations of Practice - Vignette-based Approaches in the Project coReflect@maths ..... 283&#13;
Barbara H. Leitherer, Pankaj R. Dwarka, Entela K. Xhane &amp; Jignasa R. Rami  | Undergraduate Research in a 2-Year College: Climate Change, Global Learning, Process and Observations ..... 289&#13;
Hadas Levi Gamlieli, Alon Pinto &amp; Boris Koichu | Secondary-Tertiary Transition and Effective Ways of Coping with it: A Perspective of Lecturers ..... 295&#13;
Sigal Levy &amp; Yelena Stukalin | Introducing Main Statistical Concepts to Non-statisticians ..... 301&#13;
Nicole Lewis, Ryan Andrew Nivens, Jamie Price, Jennifer Price &amp; Anant Godbole | Pandemic-Driven Mathematical Initiatives within the East Tennessee State University Center of STEM Education ..... 304&#13;
Po-Hung Liu | Students' Perceptions of Paradoxes of the Infinity ..... 310&#13;
Hong Lu &amp; Xin Chen | The Relationship between Teacher-student Relationship, Interest, Self-efficacy and Mathematics Achievement – Does Gender Play a Role in it? ..... 316&#13;
Cheryl Ann Lubinski &amp; Allison Kroesch | Developing, Not Teaching, Problem-Solving Strategies ..... 322&#13;
Jürgen Maaß | Professional Mathematical Modelling: What we can Learn about Teaching Real World Mathematics from the Real Application of Mathematics in our World? ..... 325&#13;
Jodelle S. W. Magner &amp; Susan McMillen | Making Word Problems Accessible to All: Innovating through Meaningful&#13;
Models ..... 331&#13;
Rafael Alberto Méndez-Romero &amp; María Angélica Suavita-Ramírez | The mINNga Labs: an Initiative of the Universidad del Rosario to Strengthen STEM Skills, Social Sensitivity and Youth Empowerment in Colombia ..... 333&#13;
Jennifer Missen | A Process for Updating Mathematics Teaching for 21st Century Students ..... 338&#13;
Shelby Morge &amp; Christopher Gordon | Using Squeak Etoys to Model Mathematical Ideas ..... 344&#13;
Janina Morska | New Methods and Forms of Work during Online Maths Lessons ..... 350&#13;
Patricia S. Moyer-Packenham | Relationships among Semiotic Representational Transformations and Math Outcomes in Digital Games ..... 354&#13;
Svenja Müller &amp; Anna Fath-Streb | Risk Literacy in the Context of Stochastics and Mathematical Education ..... 355&#13;
M. Estela Navarro Robles | Elementary Teachers Reaching a Quasi-complete Knowledge of Rational Numbers through an Online Course ..... 361&#13;
Benita P. Nel | Noticing through Self-reflection by Mathematics Teachers using Video Stimulated Recall ..... 367&#13;
Zanele Ngcobo | Evoking School Mathematical Knowledge among Preservice Secondary Mathematics Teachers through Error Analysis ..... 373&#13;
Jenna O'Dell &amp; Todd Frauenholtz | Recruiting Mathematics and Mathematics Education Majors to a University….374&#13;
Elizabeth Oldham &amp; Aibhín Bray | Undergraduate Mathematics Students' Reflections on School Mathematics Curricula after a Major Curriculum Change in Ireland ..... 378&#13;
Nick Vincent Otuma | Mismatch between Spoken Language and Visual Representation of Mathematical Concepts ..... 384&#13;
Jenny Pange &amp; Alina Degteva | Project-based Learning in Statistics ..... 389&#13;
Andrea Peter-Koop | School-Readiness in Mathematics: Development of a Screening Test for Children Starting School ..... 395&#13;
Maria Piccione &amp; Francesca Ricci | The Importance of Early Developing Symbol-sense ..... 401&#13;
Maria Piccione &amp; Francesca Ricci | Activities and tools for Early Developing Symbol-sense ..... 407&#13;
Shelley B. Poole | The "Yes, and…" Approach to Teaching Mathematical Modelling ..... 413&#13;
Jordan T. Register &amp; Christian H. Andersson | Analysing PSTs Ethical Reasoning in a Data Driven World ..... 418&#13;
Sarah A. Roberts, Cameron Dexter Torti &amp; Julie A. Bianchini | A Mathematics Specialist Supporting District Shifts in Instruction for Multilingual Learners through Studio Days ..... 424&#13;
Keith Robins | Applying Mathematical Thinking Principles to Real Life Situations to Create an Objective Thinking Strategy ..... 429&#13;
Christine Robinson &amp; Karen Singer-Freeman | Digital Enhancements for Common, Online Mathematics Courses ..... 434&#13;
Ann-Sofi Röj-Lindberg | Trends in Mathematics Education in Finland ..... 439&#13;
Sheena Rughubar-Reddy &amp; Emma Engers | Video Tutorials and Quick Response Codes to Assist Mathematical Literacy Students in a Non-classroom Environment ..... 445&#13;
Sheryl J. Rushton, Melina Alexander &amp; Shirley Dawson | Mathematics to Teacher Education Persistence ..... 451&#13;
Robyn Ruttenberg-Rozen | In-the-Moment Narratives: Interventions with Learners Experiencing Mathematics Difficulties ..... 457&#13;
Tanishq Kumar Sah | Extension of Theories ..... 463&#13;
Ishola A. Salami &amp; Temitope O. Ajani | Mathematics Songs to Hip-hop Music: Power to Engage Pupils and Improve Learning Outcomes in Primary Mathematics ..... 466&#13;
S R Santhanam | Teaching Mathematics using Storytelling and Technology ..... 472&#13;
Ipek Saralar-Aras &amp; Betul Esen | Designing Lessons for the 5th Graders through a Design Study on Teaching&#13;
Polygons ..... 476&#13;
Stephanie Sheehan-Braine &amp; Irina Lyublinskaya | A Framework for Online Problem-Based Learning for Mathematics Educators ..... 482&#13;
M. Vali Siadat | Keystone Model of Teaching and Learning in Mathematics ..... 488&#13;
Parmjit Singh, Nurul Akma Md Nasir &amp; Teoh Sian Hoon | The Dearth of Development in Mathematical Thinking Among High School Leavers ..... 494&#13;
Praneetha Singh | Mathovation- Creativity and Innovation in the Mathematics Classroom ..... 500&#13;
Charles Raymond Smith &amp; Cyril Julie | Towards Understanding Integrating Digital Technologies in the Mathematics Classroom ..... 506&#13;
Panagiotis Stefanides | "Generator Polyhedron", Icosahedron Non-Regular, Discovered Invention ..... 512&#13;
Michelle Stephan &amp; David Pugalee | The Future of Mathematics Education in the Digital Age ..... 518&#13;
Yelena Stukalin &amp; Sigal Levy | Introducing Probability Theory to Ultra-Orthodox Jewish Students by Examples from the Bible and Ancient Scripts ..... 522&#13;
Emily K. Suh, Lisa Hoffman &amp; Alan Zollman | STEM SMART: Five Essential Life Skills Students Need for their Future ..... 526&#13;
Janet (Hagemeyer) Tassell, Jessica Hussung, Kylie Bray, Darby Tassell &amp; Haley (Clayton) Carbone | Elementary Pre-Service Teachers' Beliefs about Mathematics Fluency: Transforming Through Readings &amp; Discussions ..... 531&#13;
Eleni Tsami, Dimitra Kouloumpou &amp; Andreas Rokopanos | The Gender Gap in Statistics Courses: A Contemporary View on a Statistics Department ..... 537&#13;
Ching-Yu Tseng, Paul Foster, Jake Klinkert, Elizabeth Adams, Corey Clark, Eric C. Larson &amp; Leanne Ketterlin-Geller | Using Cognitive Walkthroughs to Evaluate the Students' Computational Thinking during Gameplay ..... 542&#13;
Ariana-Stanca Vacaretu | GROWE in Math ..... 548&#13;
Shin Watanabe &amp; Takako Aoki | In School and Out School ..... 554&#13;
Laura Watkins, Patrick Kimani, April Ström, Bismark Akoto, Dexter Lim | Representational Competence with Linear Functions: A Glimpse into the Community College Algebra Classroom ..... 560&#13;
Ian Willson | Formative Assessment Activities for Introductory Calculus ..... 566&#13;
Kay A. Wohlhuter &amp; Mary B. Swarthout | Number Talks: Working to Deepen and Grow Number Sense Knowledge ..... 569&#13;
Ryan G. Zonnefeld &amp; Valorie L. Zonnefeld  | Rural STEM Teachers: An Oasis in the Desert ..... 574&#13;
Valorie L. Zonnefeld | Pedagogies that Foster a Growth Mindset Towards Mathematics ..... 580</mods:tableOfContents>
                  <mods:targetAudience>specialized</mods:targetAudience>
                  <mods:note type="additional physical form">Druckausgabe: Morska, Janina; Rogerson, Alan (Hrsg.): The Mathematics Education for the Future Project : King's College, Cambridge Aug 8-13, 2022 : Proceedings of the 16th International Conference : Building on the Past to Prepare for the Future. Münster : WTM, 2022. (Conference Proceedings in Mathematics Education ; 7), ISBN 978-3-95987-217-1</mods:note>
                  <mods:note type="ownership">© 2022 WTM – Verlag für wissenschaftliche Texte und Medien, Münster</mods:note>
                  <mods:subject>
                    <mods:topic lang="ger">Konferenz; mathematische Erziehung</mods:topic>
                  </mods:subject>
                  <mods:classification authority="ddc">510</mods:classification>
                  <mods:classification authority="ddc">370</mods:classification>
                  <mods:relatedItem type="series">
                    <mods:titleInfo>
                      <mods:title script="Latn">Conference proceedings in mathematics education</mods:title>
                    </mods:titleInfo>
                    <mods:part type="volume" order="7">
                      <mods:detail>
                        <mods:number>7</mods:number>
                      </mods:detail>
                    </mods:part>
                    <mods:recordInfo>
                      <mods:recordIdentifier>oai:wwu.de:4cb868bf-7636-49d7-82fa-a70f54b19631</mods:recordIdentifier>
                    </mods:recordInfo>
                  </mods:relatedItem>
                  <mods:relatedItem otherType="IsIdenticalTo" otherTypeAuth="datacite">
                    <mods:identifier type="doi">10.37626/GA9783959872188.0</mods:identifier>
                  </mods:relatedItem>
                  <mods:identifier type="urn">urn:nbn:de:hbz:6-43059711110</mods:identifier>
                  <mods:identifier type="doi">10.17879/43059715851</mods:identifier>
                  <mods:identifier type="isbn">978-3-95987-218-8</mods:identifier>
                  <mods:location>
                    <mods:url access="object in context">https://miami.uni-muenster.de/Record/5f210d40-7a28-4b7e-b8b6-9305c3a13337</mods:url>
                  </mods:location>
                  <mods:accessCondition type="restriction on access">
                    <mods:extension>
                      <ma:maWrap xmlns:ma="http://memoryalpha.ulb.uni-muenster.de">
                        <ma:licence>
                          <ma:displayLabel>InC 1.0</ma:displayLabel>
                          <ma:targetUrl>https://rightsstatements.org/vocab/InC/1.0/</ma:targetUrl>
                        </ma:licence>
                      </ma:maWrap>
                    </mods:extension>
                  </mods:accessCondition>
                  <mods:recordInfo>
                    <mods:recordIdentifier>oai:wwu.de:5f210d40-7a28-4b7e-b8b6-9305c3a13337</mods:recordIdentifier>
                  </mods:recordInfo>
                </mods:mods>
              </mets:xmlData>
            </mets:mdWrap>
          </mets:dmdSec>
          <mets:amdSec ID="AMD_5f210d40-7a28-4b7e-b8b6-9305c3a13337">
            <mets:rightsMD ID="RIGHTSMD_5f210d40-7a28-4b7e-b8b6-9305c3a13337">
              <mets:mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" MIMETYPE="text/xml" OTHERMDTYPE="DVRIGHTS">
                <mets:xmlData>
                  <dv:rights xmlns:dv="http://dfg-viewer.de/">
                    <dv:owner>Universitäts- und Landesbibliothek Münster</dv:owner>
                  </dv:rights>
                </mets:xmlData>
              </mets:mdWrap>
            </mets:rightsMD>
            <mets:digiprovMD ID="DIGIPROVMD_5f210d40-7a28-4b7e-b8b6-9305c3a13337">
              <mets:mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" MIMETYPE="text/xml" OTHERMDTYPE="DVLINKS">
                <mets:xmlData>
                  <dv:links xmlns:dv="http://dfg-viewer.de/">
                    <dv:reference>https://miami.uni-muenster.de/Record/5f210d40-7a28-4b7e-b8b6-9305c3a13337</dv:reference>
                    <dv:presentation/>
                  </dv:links>
                </mets:xmlData>
              </mets:mdWrap>
            </mets:digiprovMD>
          </mets:amdSec>
          <mets:fileSec>
            <mets:fileGrp USE="DEFAULT">
              <mets:file MIMETYPE="application/pdf" CHECKSUM="ab491a9689b2b7e8cecfa22263ef8e80f46980862243cf220b4fec8da9429acf" CREATED="2022-07-01T08:05:39" CHECKSUMTYPE="SHA-256" SIZE="13151830" ID="ID_FIL_wtm_isbn-978-3-95987-218-8.pdf_DEFAULT">
                <mets:FLocat xlink:href="https://repositorium.uni-muenster.de/document/miami/5f210d40-7a28-4b7e-b8b6-9305c3a13337/wtm_isbn-978-3-95987-218-8.pdf" LOCTYPE="URL"/>
              </mets:file>
            </mets:fileGrp>
            <mets:fileGrp USE="DOWNLOAD">
              <mets:file MIMETYPE="application/pdf" ID="DOW5f210d40-7a28-4b7e-b8b6-9305c3a13337">
                <mets:FLocat xlink:href="https://repositorium.uni-muenster.de/transfer/miami/5f210d40-7a28-4b7e-b8b6-9305c3a13337" LOCTYPE="URL"/>
              </mets:file>
            </mets:fileGrp>
          </mets:fileSec>
          <mets:structMap TYPE="PHYSICAL">
            <mets:div ID="ID_PHY_5f210d40-7a28-4b7e-b8b6-9305c3a13337" TYPE="physSequence">
              <mets:div ID="ID_PHY_wtm_isbn-978-3-95987-218-8.pdf">
                <mets:fptr FILEID="ID_FIL_wtm_isbn-978-3-95987-218-8.pdf_DEFAULT"/>
              </mets:div>
            </mets:div>
          </mets:structMap>
          <mets:structMap TYPE="LOGICAL">
            <mets:div ADMID="AMD_5f210d40-7a28-4b7e-b8b6-9305c3a13337" DMDID="DMD_5f210d40-7a28-4b7e-b8b6-9305c3a13337" ID="ID_LOG_5f210d40-7a28-4b7e-b8b6-9305c3a13337" TYPE="Monograph">
              <mets:div ID="ID_LOG_ID_PHY_wtm_isbn-978-3-95987-218-8.pdf"/>
            </mets:div>
          </mets:structMap>
          <mets:structLink>
            <mets:smLink xlink:from="ID_LOG_5f210d40-7a28-4b7e-b8b6-9305c3a13337" xlink:to="ID_PHY_5f210d40-7a28-4b7e-b8b6-9305c3a13337"/>
            <mets:smLink xlink:from="ID_LOG_ID_PHY_wtm_isbn-978-3-95987-218-8.pdf" xlink:to="ID_PHY_wtm_isbn-978-3-95987-218-8.pdf"/>
          </mets:structLink>
        </mets:mets>